<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <template id="report_contract_template">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
			<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
				<t t-call="web.basic_layout">
					<!-- CONTAINER -->
					<div class="page" style="font-size: 12px">
					    
					    <t t-set="months" t-value="{                             '1': 'enero',                             '2': 'febrero',                             '3': 'marzo',                             '4': 'abril',                             '5': 'mayo',                             '6': 'junio',                             '7': 'julio',                             '8': 'agosto',                             '9': 'septiembre',                             '10': 'octubre',                             '11': 'noviembre',                             '12': 'diciembre'                         }"/>
					    
					    <t t-set="document_types" t-value="{                             'Factura': 'Factura Consumidor Final',                              'CCF': 'Comprobante de Crédito fiscal',                             'FSUJEx': 'Factura de sujeto excluido'                         }"/>
                        
                        <t t-set="tipo_fact" t-value="document_types.get(doc.partner_id.property_account_position_id.sv_document, '')"/>

                        <div class="row mb-4">
                            <div class="col-3">
                                <img t-if="doc.company_id.logo" t-att-src="image_data_uri(doc.company_id.logo)" style="max-height: 100px; margin-left: 2mm" alt="Company Logo"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-5"/>
                            <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                <h5>
                                    <strong>Contract No. </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.cabal_sequence"/>
                                </h5>
                                <h5 class="mt-2">
                                    <strong>Client Code </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.id "/>
                                </h5>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Header -->
                        <h5 t-translation="on">CLIENT INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Client Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong t-translation="on">Client Details</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></div>
                                        <t t-if="tipo_fact == 'Factura Consumidor Final'">
                                            <div t-translation="on">DUI: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_dui"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                        <t t-else="">
                                            <div t-translation="on">NIT: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nit"/></div>
                                            <div t-translation="on">NRC: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nrc"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong t-translation="on">Service Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Billing Info Header -->
                        <h5 t-translation="on">BILLING INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Billing Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong t-translation="on">Billing Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong t-translation="on">Contacts</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div t-translation="on">Email: <span class="bg-light p-1"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/></span></div>
                                        <div t-translation="on">Telephone: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/></div>
                                        <div t-translation="on">Whatsapp: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></div>
                                        <div t-translation="on">Telephone Mobile: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.mobile"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row mt-1">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-3">
                                        <strong t-translation="on">Type of Invoicing</strong>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-0">
                                        <span t-esc="tipo_fact"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <!-- Authorization Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-4 font-italic"  t-translation="on">
                                The client authorizes the delivery of his/her invoice in electronic format by email, SMS or WhatsApp. A copy of the contract conditions will be sent by the same means.
                            </div>

                        </div>
                        
                        <h5 t-translation="on">SERVICES CONTRACTED</h5>

                        <!-- Services Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <!-- Get recurring products and total -->
                            <t t-set="recurring_lines" t-value="doc.order_line.filtered(lambda l: l.product_template_id.recurring_invoice)"/>
                            <t t-set="monthly_total" t-value="sum(recurring_lines.mapped('price_unit'))"/>
                            
                            <!-- Products List -->
                            <t t-foreach="recurring_lines" t-as="line">
                                <div class="row mb-2">
                                    <div class="col-12">
                                        <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1" t-translation="on">
                                            Plan: <t t-esc="line.name"/>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </t>
                        
                            <!-- Contract and Payment Info -->
                            <div class="row mt-3">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1" t-translation="on">
                                        Contract Length <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6 text-right">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1" t-translation="on">
                                        Monthy Payment: US$ <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <!-- Late Payment Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-3 px-2" t-translation="on">
                                Late payment fee - 5%
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    
                        <!-- Declaration Text -->
                        <div class="mt-4" style="font-size: 0.9em;" t-translation="on">
                            I declare that my personal information is true and authorize the companies to verify its authenticity, prior to processing the request for services. I accept that the documentation containing the information provided for the purposes of this contract will be safeguarded by the company. I attest to the provisions of this form and annexes. I confirm that I have read and understand the contract and the conditions of the contract, which were presented to me by the company's staff. I ratify the content of the same and sign.
                        </div>
                        
                        <!-- Signature Section -->
                        <div class="mt-4 border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong t-translation="on">Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p> 
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong t-translation="on">Company Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn2/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.user_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                        </div>
                        
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h5 class="m-0" t-translation="on">PROMISE WITHOUT PROTEST</h5>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-end" t-translation="on">
                                    Por US$ <strong><t t-esc="doc.contract_value" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/></strong>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                TAMANIQUE, 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.day"/ t-translation="on"> de 
                                <t t-esc="months[str(doc.start_date.month)]"/ t-translation="on"> de 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.year"/> 
                                We will PAY without protest unconditionally to the order of REDES LITORALES S.A. DE C.V., at its offices, on the _______ day of _________ of the year _________ the amount of
                                <span class="font-weight-bold">
                                    <t t-esc="doc.contract_value_amount_to_text()"/> 
                                    OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
                                </span>, 
                                plus the conventional interest of ONE POINT ZERO ZERO percent per month, calculated from the date of signing of this document, I(we) will also pay, from this last date, default interest on the outstanding principal balance.
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong t-translation="on">Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4">
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h4 class="m-0">TERMINOS</h4>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                1. PURPOSE. REDES LITORALES, S.A. de C.V. (hereinafter REDES LITORALES or CABAL), hereinafter referred to as 'the company', shall provide wireless Internet browsing services, dedicated Internet access, and other additional and/or value-added services through its telecommunications infrastructure. The services are provided to the CLIENT in its capacity as recipient or end user thereof, and based on the provisions now established in this document or any of its annexes.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                2. RATES, BILLING AND PAYMENT. The CLIENT shall pay the company the rates corresponding to each of the contracted services, as agreed in the contract. Additionally, the CLIENT shall pay the amounts resulting from any supplementary and/or value-added services used, and the rates for transfers, uninstallations and disconnections. Payments shall be billed in United States dollars, for monthly periods, according to the billing systems used by the company. The CLIENT must pay the invoices on the dates stipulated therein. Such payments may be made at any of the following locations according to preference and availability: CABAL Service Centers, banking and/or financial institutions and/or any other means authorized for this purpose by the company. The corresponding late payment charge will be applied for each service, according to the amount stipulated in the contract. The invoices will reflect the concepts for the services used. Failure to receive the invoice does not inhibit the payment obligation derived from the provision of services, and it is the responsibility of the client to notify the company of this situation. The company, with prior authorization from the client, may deliver invoices by any electronic means. ELECTRONIC BILLING: The sending of invoices by electronic means will be governed by the following conditions: (a) The sending of invoices by electronic means exempts the company from sending the physical invoice to the CLIENT's correspondence address. (b) The company will issue the invoice electronically in accordance with its internal processes and once issued will send it by the electronic means selected by the CLIENT, who will be responsible for the monthly verification of its receipt. (c) The CLIENT recognizes, understands and accepts that it is his responsibility to have the availability to receive the invoice by the electronic means selected by him. (d) In the event that the CLIENT does not receive the invoice in the designated means, his responsibility for payment will not be exempted, and he must also notify the company of this situation. (e) In the event that the CLIENT designates more than one means, the company will give priority to email.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                3. DURATION AND TERMINATION. The duration of the contracted services will be specified in the contract or its annexes. It may be a mandatory or indefinite period, starting from the installation, activation, use and/or programming of the services, and will continue until the client decides to cancel it. 3.1. RIGHT TO UNSUBSCRIBE: The CLIENT has the right to unsubscribe in accordance with the provisions of article 13-8 of the Consumer Protection Law. To make use of such right, THE CLIENT must notify the company ten (10) business days in advance of the time when it is to take effect. In the case of unsubscribing before the expiration of the mandatory period, the penalty established in clause fifteen must be paid. 3.2. CONTINUITY OF SERVICES: Once the agreed mandatory period has ended or when there is no mandatory period agreed by the parties, without the client requesting cancellation, the services will continue to be provided indefinitely, and the client may cancel at any time by notifying ten (10) business days in advance of the time when the cancellation is to take effect, without incurring any penalty. 3.3. GENERAL TERMINATION: The agreed mandatory term may also be terminated by: The general causes of termination of contracts, those established by law, likewise the company will have the right to terminate it in the following cases: a) when the CLIENT improperly uses the services, commits telecommunications fraud or makes illicit use of the services b) When the CLIENT is in arrears for more than two (2) consecutive months, and c) When THE CLIENT requests the provision of services in places other than those established in the contract or in places where the company is physically or technically unable to provide them. The termination of the provision of services will not exempt the CLIENT from its obligations to the company for the goods and services received. THE CLIENT accepts that the company may notify him of the termination of the mandatory term of this contract through technical means according to availability and convenience. 3.4. AUTOMATIC RENEWAL: This contract will automatically renew for an additional period of twelve (12) months at the end of the initial term, unless the CLIENT notifies the company in writing of its intention to terminate the contract at least thirty (30) days prior to the contract end date. The termination notice must be sent by email to cancelservice@cabal.sv or in person at any of the company offices. In the event of automatic renewal, all conditions and terms of the original contract will continue to apply during the renewal period.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                4. ACTIVATION, OWNERSHIP OF EQUIPMENT AND OPERATION OF THE SERVICE. The services will be provided only through the accesses, numbers and/or authorizations that the company delivers or carries out in favor of THE CLIENT. The equipment provided to provide the contracted services will be understood to be delivered to THE CLIENT in the capacity indicated in the contract. The equipment delivered on loan and/or lease is the property of the company. The equipment delivered to THE CLIENT as a purchase, donation or installment sale is the property of THE CLIENT as long as the conditions agreed in this instrument or its annexes are met. The delivery of the equipment, depending on the service, will be carried out through the issuance of a delivery and/or installation order, which will be signed by the user, or failing that, by the person who is at the installation address indicated by the CLIENT. In the event of theft, robbery or loss of the equipment, it is the responsibility of the CUSTOMER to notify the company for the immediate blocking of the services and the corresponding complaint must be filed with the competent authorities, sending a certified copy of the complaint to any of the company's Service Centers within the following five (5) days of its filing. The loss, destruction, deterioration, robbery, theft or misplacement of the equipment does not inhibit the obligation of payment derived from the provision of the services that are available to the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                5. COMMERCIAL WARRANTY. The equipment provided for the provision of services will be covered by the warranty granted by its manufacturers and will therefore be subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product, unless otherwise provided in a special document attached to this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                6. QUALITY, COVERAGE AND MAINTENANCE OF THE SERVICE. The company will provide its services in accordance with the quality levels, parameters and methods established in the current legislation and the conditions of this contract and/or any of its annexes. In any case, the user specifically acknowledges that he/she has all the information regarding the coverage and quality of the services provided. The company will provide the service exclusively in the coverage areas within the national territory in which it is implemented, according to the coverage information of each service available in any of the company's Service Centers. The CUSTOMER understands that mobile services and internet services may be affected by structural, orographic and/or atmospheric conditions, improper handling by the user, number of connected users, or any other situation that prevents, makes impossible or degrades their provision, in which case action will be taken in accordance with the provisions of current legislation. In the case of residential services, THE CUSTOMER acknowledges that they will be provided at the address and domicile provided at the time of contracting. The company will provide preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure, equipment and/or networks for the provision of services, so that, if breakdowns, interruptions or malfunctions of the services occur due to unforeseen circumstances or force majeure, the company will repair the faults or breakdowns that have occurred as soon as possible. The company will not be responsible for damage to the configuration and/or operation of the equipment owned by the user, once the service has been installed/activated to the user's complete satisfaction.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                7. TEMPORARY SUSPENSION OF SERVICES. The company may suspend services without prior notice in cases permitted by current legislation. The company, after giving prior notice to THE CLIENT, may suspend services in the following cases: indication of telecommunications fraud, illicit use of the service or late payment of the client's services. When the company must make a general, temporary and continuous suspension of any of the services, the company will make the corresponding notices in accordance with the law; in these cases, the company will not be responsible for damages caused by the suspension, nor will it be grounds for breach of contract. The CLIENT accepts the limitation of use of any of the services and it will take place when the credit limit has been exceeded, when there are outstanding invoices to be paid or when the blocking of supplementary and/or value-added services has been requested.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                8. CREDIT LIMIT. The company makes available to the CUSTOMER a consumer credit for each contracted service, which will be determined and subsequently modified at the CUSTOMER's request, based on his/her credit behavior.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                9. PAYMENT GUARANTEES. The CLIENT makes available to each service provider a negotiable instrument that will support the payment of the amounts resulting from any of the services used and the total value of the equipment provided. The negotiable instrument will be returned, at the request of the client, within fifteen (15) business days following the effective date of termination of all services, after payment of all outstanding obligations. In addition to the above, the CLIENT will make available to the company any other type of guarantees for the Formation and execution of this contract, which will be contained in documents attached to this instrument.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                10. SECRECY OF COMMUNICATIONS. The company will adopt the necessary technical and organisational measures in accordance with current legislation in order to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications. In any case, the company shall be exonerated from all liability arising from the illegal obtaining of material and/or information, its use or publicity by third parties, and in general, from any actions or omissions, including those of government entities, which, not being attributable to the company, constitute a breach of the secrecy of communications.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                11. ASSIGNMENT. THE CLIENT may not assign this contract, or the services acquired, to third parties without the prior written consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to affiliates and/or subsidiaries belonging to the company.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                12. INFORMATION ABOUT THE SERVICES. The company will provide the CUSTOMER with the necessary and convenient information for an adequate provision of the service, which may be provided on social media, Service Centers, Call Centers, on its website, points of sale or authorized marketers. In the event that the CUSTOMER requests specific information about the provision of the services, the company will provide it free of charge. Likewise, the CUSTOMER agrees to receive information regarding the contracted products and services through technical means such as email, fax, short messages, television, telephone and any other technology that allows remote communication. The CUSTOMER establishes as a means of notification, the physical and electronic addresses, telephone numbers and other data provided in this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                13. VALIDATION OF TECHNICAL MEANS. The parties acknowledge the validity of the electronic and/or telematic data and procedures for the provision and incorporation of services. The client expressly agrees that technical means may be used to express the CLIENT's consent for the modification, incorporation and/or deletion of available services, including value-added services. The CLIENT is responsible for the diligent custody and maintenance of the confidentiality of its information, as well as passwords, access keys, encrypted systems or communication encryption systems, which are provided by the company. These mechanisms will be understood to be used only by the CLIENT.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                14. MODIFICATION OF THE CONTRACT. THE CLIENT may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through any of the means established in clause thirteen (13) of this instrument; once accepted, it will be understood that the terms, conditions, price and term of the same have been agreed upon.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                15. PENALTIES. The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper or illegal use of the services, breach of contract and other causes that are applicable under Salvadoran legislation. In the event of early termination of the mandatory term, the CLIENT must pay the company the value of the goods and services received on the effective date of termination. In turn, the CLIENT will pay the company an amount equivalent to the damage caused by the early termination of the contract as a penalty, which will be an amount equivalent to the basic charges for the services required to terminate the contract; if the client was delivered devices in a quality other than a installment sale, action will be taken in accordance with the equipment annex.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                16. CUSTOMER SERVICE. There is a customer service area available to the CUSTOMER at any of the Service Centers and Call Centers where they can direct requests for information about the contracted services.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                17. HANDLING COMPLAINTS. The CUSTOMER may submit complaints related to the provision of services at the Service Centers provided by the company for this purpose. When the complaint has been resolved, the company will inform the CUSTOMER of the solution adopted through the means designated by the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                18. APPLICABLE LEGISLATION AND DOMICILE. The parties agree that these general conditions and/or their annexes are subject to the legislation of the Republic of El Salvador, and any conflicts arising therefrom are subject to the rules of jurisdiction and competence of common legislation.
                            </div>

                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                19. MAINTENANCE OF CONTACT INFORMATION AND NOTIFICATION OF INTERRUPTIONS. 19.1. The CLIENT agrees to keep his/her address, telephone number and email address up to date. Any change in this information must be communicated to the company immediately. 19.2. The CLIENT must respond to calls, emails or other communications from the company in a timely manner. 19.3. The CLIENT must inform the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for any damage or loss of service that occurs prior to notification. The notification must be sent to the email address meayuda@cabal.sv or notified by telephone, in which case the client will receive a ticket number to record the notification.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                RESIDENTIAL INTERNET SERVICE. The Internet service will be provided under the following conditions: 1) The CUSTOMER will use the service only from the interconnection protocol number assigned by the company and the technical requirements of the CUSTOMER's equipment indicated for this purpose; 2) Continuously, twenty-four hours a day, every day of the year, during the validity of the contracted period for the provision of the service, at the speed established in the selected plan. THE CUSTOMER understands that the navigation speed depends on various technical factors, such as: characteristics and quantity of the equipment connected to the network, incompatibility with other technology or software used by the customer, among others similar, and in case of compensation, action will be taken in accordance with current law. 3) The CUSTOMER will guarantee the electrical installations, associated protection equipment and the appropriate computer equipment to access the service. 4) Under current national and international legislation that ensures intellectual property rights, protection of minors, data protection and others; the use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute an infringement of such legislation; Consequently, the company, by administrative or judicial request, is obliged to reveal the information regarding the ownership of the connection from which the improper use of the network originated. In these cases, the CUSTOMER assumes all responsibility arising from the improper use of the service; 5) The CUSTOMER may at any time improve the contracted service through the various technical means made available by the company.*
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify" t-translation="on">
                                EQUIPMENT ANNEX. For the purposes of providing the services described in the general contracting conditions, modems, routers, decoder boxes, among others necessary for communications, shall be understood as equipment. The company may make available to the CLIENT, according to the contracted and selected conditions, the equipment in accordance with the following stipulations: l. LOAN CONDITIONS. The company will be the owner of the equipment delivered to the CLIENT for the provision of services, and the CLIENT is obliged to maintain due diligence and care of the same; the latter being responsible for the resulting breakdowns when they are attributable to it; otherwise, the company must replace the goods at the request of the CLIENT and when, at the company's discretion, it is required. Likewise, in the event of restitution of equipment, for example, due to contractual termination, THE CLIENT must return it to the company within a maximum period of ten (10) business days; otherwise, THE CLIENT acknowledges that it must pay the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting. In the event that the CUSTOMER contracts residential services, the following equipment will be delivered on loan: main digital box, Cable Modem, and Router. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. 11. LEASE CONDITIONS. The value of the equipment delivered on lease will be determined, where applicable, in the commercial or promotional conditions. The CUSTOMER acknowledges that the equipment is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contractual relationship. During the duration of the lease, the CUSTOMER is obliged to maintain due diligence and care for it, being responsible for loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. The Customer must pay the administrative cost determined by THE COMPANY for the removal of the equipment. 111. CONDITIONS OF THE DONATION SUBJECT TO CONDITION. The equipment delivered at no cost to THE CLIENT will be deemed free of charge provided that the latter complies with both the general terms and conditions of the contract, as well as the mandatory term of validity. THE CLIENT undertakes to maintain due diligence and care of the equipment, being responsible for the loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. In the event of early termination of the contract, THE CLIENT undertakes to pay the company the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting, in addition to any applicable penalties, in accordance with the provisions of the conditions of this contract. IV. TERM: The term of the loan and/or lease and/or installment sale will be that agreed upon according to the commercial or promotional conditions or those established in this instrument. V. DELIVERY OF THE EQUIPMENT. In this act, the CLIENT accepts and receives to his satisfaction the equipment in perfect working order, having been inspected and made available to him, prior to its physical delivery.
                            </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4" t-translation="on">
                            <h3>Friendly Summary of Internet Service Contract</h3>
                            <h4>(not part of the contract - for information only)</h4>
                    
                            <h5>Client Information</h5>
                            <p><strong>Name:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Service Address:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Contact:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></p>

                            <h5>Conditions</h5>
                            <p><strong>Length of Contract:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Monthly Payment:</strong> <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{'widget': 'float', 'precision': 2}"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Late Payment Fee:</strong> 5%</p>

                            <h5>Customer Rights and Responsibilities</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Object of the Agreement:</strong> The company will provide Internet browsing services and other additional services through its telecommunications infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Rates, Billing and Payment:</strong> The client will pay the agreed fees on a monthly basis. Invoices will be sent electronically. The client must pay the invoices on the stipulated dates. Failure to receive the invoice does not exempt the obligation to pay.</li>
                                <li><strong>Duration and Termination:</strong> The contract has a specified duration and can be automatically renewed for 12 months if the client does not notify its intention to terminate it with 30 days' notice. The client can cancel the service with 10 days' notice, subject to penalties if canceled before the mandatory term.</li>
                                <li><strong>Ownership and Use of Equipment:</strong> The equipment provided is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contract. In the event of loss or damage to the equipment, the client must notify the company immediately.</li>
                                <li><strong>Equipment Warranty:</strong> The equipment has a manufacturer's warranty and is subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Quality and Maintenance:</strong> The company will provide the services in accordance with the established quality levels and will perform preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Suspension of Services:</strong> The company may suspend services without prior notice in certain cases permitted by law, such as indications of fraud or late payment.</li>
                                <li><strong>Credit Limit:</strong> The company establishes a credit limit for each contracted service, which may be modified at the request of the client.</li>
                                <li><strong>Payment Guarantees:</strong> The client must provide payment guarantees, such as a security, that support the amounts resulting from the services used.</li>
                                <li><strong>Secrecy of Communications:</strong> The company will take measures to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications, but will not be responsible for the illegal obtaining of information by third parties.</li>
                                <li><strong>Assignment of the Contract:</strong> The client cannot assign the contract to third parties without the prior consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to its subsidiaries.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Information:</strong> The company will provide the client with the necessary information for an adequate provision of the service.</li>
                                <li><strong>Validation of Technical Means:</strong> The parties recognize the validity of the electronic data and procedures for the provision of services.</li>
                                <li><strong>Modification of the Contract:</strong> The client may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through the established means.</li>
                                <li><strong>Penalties:</strong> The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper use of the services or breach of contract.</li>
                                <li><strong>Customer Service:</strong> The company offers support through its Service Centers and Call Center.</li>
                                <li><strong>Claims Service:</strong> The client may submit claims related to the provision of services at the Service Centers </li>
                                <li><strong>Applicable Law:</strong> The contract is governed by the laws of the Republic of El Salvador.</li>
                                <li><strong>Maintenance of Contact Information and Notification of Interruptions:</strong> The client must keep his contact information updated and notify the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for damages or loss of service before notification.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Residential Internet Service</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The client will use the service from the assigned protocol number and will guarantee the appropriate electrical installations and equipment.</li>
                                <li>The use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute a violation of current legislation.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Equipment Annex</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The equipment necessary for the provision of services will be provided by the company under conditions of loan, lease or donation subject to conditions.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>
                        </div> 
                    </div>
				</t>
			</t>
		</t>
    </template>
    
<!-- Template for Business Customers -->
    <template id="business_contract_template">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
			<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
				<t t-call="web.basic_layout">
					<!-- CONTAINER -->
					<div class="page" style="font-size: 12px">
					    
					    <t t-set="months" t-value="{                             '1': 'enero',                             '2': 'febrero',                             '3': 'marzo',                             '4': 'abril',                             '5': 'mayo',                             '6': 'junio',                             '7': 'julio',                             '8': 'agosto',                             '9': 'septiembre',                             '10': 'octubre',                             '11': 'noviembre',                             '12': 'diciembre'                         }"/>
					    
					    <t t-set="document_types" t-value="{                             'Factura': 'Factura Consumidor Final',                              'CCF': 'Comprobante de Crédito fiscal',                             'FSUJEx': 'Factura de sujeto excluido'                         }"/>
                        
                        <t t-set="tipo_fact" t-value="document_types.get(doc.partner_id.property_account_position_id.sv_document, '')"/>

                        <div class="row mb-4">
                            <div class="col-3">
                                <img t-if="doc.company_id.logo" t-att-src="image_data_uri(doc.company_id.logo)" style="max-height: 100px; margin-left: 2mm" alt="Company Logo"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-5"/>
                            <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                <h5>
                                    <strong>Contract No. </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.cabal_sequence"/>
                                </h5>
                                <h5 class="mt-2">
                                    <strong>Client Code </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.id "/>
                                </h5>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Header -->
                        <h5>CLIENT INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Client Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Client Details</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></div>
                                        <t t-if="tipo_fact == 'Factura Consumidor Final'">
                                            <div>DUI: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_dui"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                        <t t-else="">
                                            <div>NIT: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nit"/></div>
                                            <div>NRC: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nrc"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Service Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Billing Info Header -->
                        <h5>BILLING INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Billing Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Billing Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Contacts</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div>Email: <span class="bg-light p-1"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/></span></div>
                                        <div>Telephone: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/></div>
                                        <div>Whatsapp: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></div>
                                        <div>Telephone Mobile: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.mobile"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row mt-1">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-3">
                                        <strong>Type of Invoicing</strong>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-0">
                                        <span t-esc="tipo_fact"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <!-- Authorization Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-4 font-italic">
                                The client authorizes the delivery of his/her invoice in electronic format by email, SMS or WhatsApp. A copy of the contract conditions will be sent by the same means.
                            </div>

                        </div>
                        
                        <h5>SERVICES CONTRACTED</h5>

                        <!-- Services Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <!-- Get recurring products and total -->
                            <t t-set="recurring_lines" t-value="doc.order_line.filtered(lambda l: l.product_template_id.recurring_invoice)"/>
                            <t t-set="monthly_total" t-value="sum(recurring_lines.mapped('price_unit'))"/>
                            
                            <!-- Products List -->
                            <t t-foreach="recurring_lines" t-as="line">
                                <div class="row mb-2">
                                    <div class="col-12">
                                        <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                            Plan: <t t-esc="line.name"/>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </t>
                        
                            <!-- Contract and Payment Info -->
                            <div class="row mt-3">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Contract Length <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6 text-right">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Monthy Payment: US$ <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <!-- Late Payment Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-3 px-2">
                                Late payment fee - 5%
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    
                        <!-- Declaration Text -->
                        <div class="mt-4" style="font-size: 0.9em;">
                            I declare that my personal information is true and authorize the companies to verify its authenticity, prior to processing the request for services. I accept that the documentation containing the information provided for the purposes of this contract will be safeguarded by the company. I attest to the provisions of this form and annexes. I confirm that I have read and understand the contract and the conditions of the contract, which were presented to me by the company's staff. I ratify the content of the same and sign.
                        </div>
                        
                        <!-- Signature Section -->
                        <div class="mt-4 border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p> 
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Company Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn2/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.user_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                        </div>
                        
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h5 class="m-0">PROMISE WITHOUT PROTEST</h5>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                    Por US$ <strong><t t-esc="doc.contract_value" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/></strong>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                TAMANIQUE, 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.day"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="months[str(doc.start_date.month)]"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.year"/> 
                                We will PAY without protest unconditionally to the order of REDES LITORALES S.A. DE C.V., at its offices, on the _______ day of _________ of the year _________ the amount of
                                <span class="font-weight-bold">
                                    <t t-esc="doc.contract_value_amount_to_text()"/> 
                                    OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
                                </span>, 
                                plus the conventional interest of ONE POINT ZERO ZERO percent per month, calculated from the date of signing of this document, I(we) will also pay, from this last date, default interest on the outstanding principal balance.
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4">
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h4 class="m-0">TERMINOS</h4>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                1. PURPOSE. REDES LITORALES, S.A. de C.V. (hereinafter REDES LITORALES or CABAL), hereinafter referred to as 'the company', shall provide wireless Internet browsing services, dedicated Internet access, and other additional and/or value-added services through its telecommunications infrastructure. The services are provided to the CLIENT in its capacity as recipient or end user thereof, and based on the provisions now established in this document or any of its annexes.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                2. RATES, BILLING AND PAYMENT. The CLIENT shall pay the company the rates corresponding to each of the contracted services, as agreed in the contract. Additionally, the CLIENT shall pay the amounts resulting from any supplementary and/or value-added services used, and the rates for transfers, uninstallations and disconnections. Payments shall be billed in United States dollars, for monthly periods, according to the billing systems used by the company. The CLIENT must pay the invoices on the dates stipulated therein. Such payments may be made at any of the following locations according to preference and availability: CABAL Service Centers, banking and/or financial institutions and/or any other means authorized for this purpose by the company. The corresponding late payment charge will be applied for each service, according to the amount stipulated in the contract. The invoices will reflect the concepts for the services used. Failure to receive the invoice does not inhibit the payment obligation derived from the provision of services, and it is the responsibility of the client to notify the company of this situation. The company, with prior authorization from the client, may deliver invoices by any electronic means. ELECTRONIC BILLING: The sending of invoices by electronic means will be governed by the following conditions: (a) The sending of invoices by electronic means exempts the company from sending the physical invoice to the CLIENT's correspondence address. (b) The company will issue the invoice electronically in accordance with its internal processes and once issued will send it by the electronic means selected by the CLIENT, who will be responsible for the monthly verification of its receipt. (c) The CLIENT recognizes, understands and accepts that it is his responsibility to have the availability to receive the invoice by the electronic means selected by him. (d) In the event that the CLIENT does not receive the invoice in the designated means, his responsibility for payment will not be exempted, and he must also notify the company of this situation. (e) In the event that the CLIENT designates more than one means, the company will give priority to email.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                3. DURATION AND TERMINATION. The duration of the contracted services will be specified in the contract or its annexes. It may be a mandatory or indefinite period, starting from the installation, activation, use and/or programming of the services, and will continue until the client decides to cancel it. 3.1. RIGHT TO UNSUBSCRIBE: The CLIENT has the right to unsubscribe in accordance with the provisions of article 13-8 of the Consumer Protection Law. To make use of such right, THE CLIENT must notify the company ten (10) business days in advance of the time when it is to take effect. In the case of unsubscribing before the expiration of the mandatory period, the penalty established in clause fifteen must be paid. 3.2. CONTINUITY OF SERVICES: Once the agreed mandatory period has ended or when there is no mandatory period agreed by the parties, without the client requesting cancellation, the services will continue to be provided indefinitely, and the client may cancel at any time by notifying ten (10) business days in advance of the time when the cancellation is to take effect, without incurring any penalty. 3.3. GENERAL TERMINATION: The agreed mandatory term may also be terminated by: The general causes of termination of contracts, those established by law, likewise the company will have the right to terminate it in the following cases: a) when the CLIENT improperly uses the services, commits telecommunications fraud or makes illicit use of the services b) When the CLIENT is in arrears for more than two (2) consecutive months, and c) When THE CLIENT requests the provision of services in places other than those established in the contract or in places where the company is physically or technically unable to provide them. The termination of the provision of services will not exempt the CLIENT from its obligations to the company for the goods and services received. THE CLIENT accepts that the company may notify him of the termination of the mandatory term of this contract through technical means according to availability and convenience. 3.4. AUTOMATIC RENEWAL: This contract will automatically renew for an additional period of twelve (12) months at the end of the initial term, unless the CLIENT notifies the company in writing of its intention to terminate the contract at least thirty (30) days prior to the contract end date. The termination notice must be sent by email to cancelservice@cabal.sv or in person at any of the company offices. In the event of automatic renewal, all conditions and terms of the original contract will continue to apply during the renewal period.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                4. ACTIVATION, OWNERSHIP OF EQUIPMENT AND OPERATION OF THE SERVICE. The services will be provided only through the accesses, numbers and/or authorizations that the company delivers or carries out in favor of THE CLIENT. The equipment provided to provide the contracted services will be understood to be delivered to THE CLIENT in the capacity indicated in the contract. The equipment delivered on loan and/or lease is the property of the company. The equipment delivered to THE CLIENT as a purchase, donation or installment sale is the property of THE CLIENT as long as the conditions agreed in this instrument or its annexes are met. The delivery of the equipment, depending on the service, will be carried out through the issuance of a delivery and/or installation order, which will be signed by the user, or failing that, by the person who is at the installation address indicated by the CLIENT. In the event of theft, robbery or loss of the equipment, it is the responsibility of the CUSTOMER to notify the company for the immediate blocking of the services and the corresponding complaint must be filed with the competent authorities, sending a certified copy of the complaint to any of the company's Service Centers within the following five (5) days of its filing. The loss, destruction, deterioration, robbery, theft or misplacement of the equipment does not inhibit the obligation of payment derived from the provision of the services that are available to the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                5. COMMERCIAL WARRANTY. The equipment provided for the provision of services will be covered by the warranty granted by its manufacturers and will therefore be subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product, unless otherwise provided in a special document attached to this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                6. QUALITY, COVERAGE AND MAINTENANCE OF THE SERVICE. The company will provide its services in accordance with the quality levels, parameters and methods established in the current legislation and the conditions of this contract and/or any of its annexes. In any case, the user specifically acknowledges that he/she has all the information regarding the coverage and quality of the services provided. The company will provide the service exclusively in the coverage areas within the national territory in which it is implemented, according to the coverage information of each service available in any of the company's Service Centers. The CUSTOMER understands that mobile services and internet services may be affected by structural, orographic and/or atmospheric conditions, improper handling by the user, number of connected users, or any other situation that prevents, makes impossible or degrades their provision, in which case action will be taken in accordance with the provisions of current legislation. In the case of residential services, THE CUSTOMER acknowledges that they will be provided at the address and domicile provided at the time of contracting. The company will provide preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure, equipment and/or networks for the provision of services, so that, if breakdowns, interruptions or malfunctions of the services occur due to unforeseen circumstances or force majeure, the company will repair the faults or breakdowns that have occurred as soon as possible. The company will not be responsible for damage to the configuration and/or operation of the equipment owned by the user, once the service has been installed/activated to the user's complete satisfaction.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                7. TEMPORARY SUSPENSION OF SERVICES. The company may suspend services without prior notice in cases permitted by current legislation. The company, after giving prior notice to THE CLIENT, may suspend services in the following cases: indication of telecommunications fraud, illicit use of the service or late payment of the client's services. When the company must make a general, temporary and continuous suspension of any of the services, the company will make the corresponding notices in accordance with the law; in these cases, the company will not be responsible for damages caused by the suspension, nor will it be grounds for breach of contract. The CLIENT accepts the limitation of use of any of the services and it will take place when the credit limit has been exceeded, when there are outstanding invoices to be paid or when the blocking of supplementary and/or value-added services has been requested.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                8. CREDIT LIMIT. The company makes available to the CUSTOMER a consumer credit for each contracted service, which will be determined and subsequently modified at the CUSTOMER's request, based on his/her credit behavior.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                9. PAYMENT GUARANTEES. The CLIENT makes available to each service provider a negotiable instrument that will support the payment of the amounts resulting from any of the services used and the total value of the equipment provided. The negotiable instrument will be returned, at the request of the client, within fifteen (15) business days following the effective date of termination of all services, after payment of all outstanding obligations. In addition to the above, the CLIENT will make available to the company any other type of guarantees for the Formation and execution of this contract, which will be contained in documents attached to this instrument.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                10. SECRECY OF COMMUNICATIONS. The company will adopt the necessary technical and organisational measures in accordance with current legislation in order to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications. In any case, the company shall be exonerated from all liability arising from the illegal obtaining of material and/or information, its use or publicity by third parties, and in general, from any actions or omissions, including those of government entities, which, not being attributable to the company, constitute a breach of the secrecy of communications.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                11. ASSIGNMENT. THE CLIENT may not assign this contract, or the services acquired, to third parties without the prior written consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to affiliates and/or subsidiaries belonging to the company.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                12. INFORMATION ABOUT THE SERVICES. The company will provide the CUSTOMER with the necessary and convenient information for an adequate provision of the service, which may be provided on social media, Service Centers, Call Centers, on its website, points of sale or authorized marketers. In the event that the CUSTOMER requests specific information about the provision of the services, the company will provide it free of charge. Likewise, the CUSTOMER agrees to receive information regarding the contracted products and services through technical means such as email, fax, short messages, television, telephone and any other technology that allows remote communication. The CUSTOMER establishes as a means of notification, the physical and electronic addresses, telephone numbers and other data provided in this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                13. VALIDATION OF TECHNICAL MEANS. The parties acknowledge the validity of the electronic and/or telematic data and procedures for the provision and incorporation of services. The client expressly agrees that technical means may be used to express the CLIENT's consent for the modification, incorporation and/or deletion of available services, including value-added services. The CLIENT is responsible for the diligent custody and maintenance of the confidentiality of its information, as well as passwords, access keys, encrypted systems or communication encryption systems, which are provided by the company. These mechanisms will be understood to be used only by the CLIENT.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                14. MODIFICATION OF THE CONTRACT. THE CLIENT may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through any of the means established in clause thirteen (13) of this instrument; once accepted, it will be understood that the terms, conditions, price and term of the same have been agreed upon.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                15. PENALTIES. The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper or illegal use of the services, breach of contract and other causes that are applicable under Salvadoran legislation. In the event of early termination of the mandatory term, the CLIENT must pay the company the value of the goods and services received on the effective date of termination. In turn, the CLIENT will pay the company an amount equivalent to the damage caused by the early termination of the contract as a penalty, which will be an amount equivalent to the basic charges for the services required to terminate the contract; if the client was delivered devices in a quality other than a installment sale, action will be taken in accordance with the equipment annex.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                16. CUSTOMER SERVICE. There is a customer service area available to the CUSTOMER at any of the Service Centers and Call Centers where they can direct requests for information about the contracted services.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                17. HANDLING COMPLAINTS. The CUSTOMER may submit complaints related to the provision of services at the Service Centers provided by the company for this purpose. When the complaint has been resolved, the company will inform the CUSTOMER of the solution adopted through the means designated by the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                18. APPLICABLE LEGISLATION AND DOMICILE. The parties agree that these general conditions and/or their annexes are subject to the legislation of the Republic of El Salvador, and any conflicts arising therefrom are subject to the rules of jurisdiction and competence of common legislation.
                            </div>

                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                19. MAINTENANCE OF CONTACT INFORMATION AND NOTIFICATION OF INTERRUPTIONS. 19.1. The CLIENT agrees to keep his/her address, telephone number and email address up to date. Any change in this information must be communicated to the company immediately. 19.2. The CLIENT must respond to calls, emails or other communications from the company in a timely manner. 19.3. The CLIENT must inform the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for any damage or loss of service that occurs prior to notification. The notification must be sent to the email address meayuda@cabal.sv or notified by telephone, in which case the client will receive a ticket number to record the notification.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                RESIDENTIAL INTERNET SERVICE. The Internet service will be provided under the following conditions: 1) The CUSTOMER will use the service only from the interconnection protocol number assigned by the company and the technical requirements of the CUSTOMER's equipment indicated for this purpose; 2) Continuously, twenty-four hours a day, every day of the year, during the validity of the contracted period for the provision of the service, at the speed established in the selected plan. THE CUSTOMER understands that the navigation speed depends on various technical factors, such as: characteristics and quantity of the equipment connected to the network, incompatibility with other technology or software used by the customer, among others similar, and in case of compensation, action will be taken in accordance with current law. 3) The CUSTOMER will guarantee the electrical installations, associated protection equipment and the appropriate computer equipment to access the service. 4) Under current national and international legislation that ensures intellectual property rights, protection of minors, data protection and others; the use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute an infringement of such legislation; Consequently, the company, by administrative or judicial request, is obliged to reveal the information regarding the ownership of the connection from which the improper use of the network originated. In these cases, the CUSTOMER assumes all responsibility arising from the improper use of the service; 5) The CUSTOMER may at any time improve the contracted service through the various technical means made available by the company.*
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                EQUIPMENT ANNEX. For the purposes of providing the services described in the general contracting conditions, modems, routers, decoder boxes, among others necessary for communications, shall be understood as equipment. The company may make available to the CLIENT, according to the contracted and selected conditions, the equipment in accordance with the following stipulations: l. LOAN CONDITIONS. The company will be the owner of the equipment delivered to the CLIENT for the provision of services, and the CLIENT is obliged to maintain due diligence and care of the same; the latter being responsible for the resulting breakdowns when they are attributable to it; otherwise, the company must replace the goods at the request of the CLIENT and when, at the company's discretion, it is required. Likewise, in the event of restitution of equipment, for example, due to contractual termination, THE CLIENT must return it to the company within a maximum period of ten (10) business days; otherwise, THE CLIENT acknowledges that it must pay the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting. In the event that the CUSTOMER contracts residential services, the following equipment will be delivered on loan: main digital box, Cable Modem, and Router. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. 11. LEASE CONDITIONS. The value of the equipment delivered on lease will be determined, where applicable, in the commercial or promotional conditions. The CUSTOMER acknowledges that the equipment is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contractual relationship. During the duration of the lease, the CUSTOMER is obliged to maintain due diligence and care for it, being responsible for loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. The Customer must pay the administrative cost determined by THE COMPANY for the removal of the equipment. 111. CONDITIONS OF THE DONATION SUBJECT TO CONDITION. The equipment delivered at no cost to THE CLIENT will be deemed free of charge provided that the latter complies with both the general terms and conditions of the contract, as well as the mandatory term of validity. THE CLIENT undertakes to maintain due diligence and care of the equipment, being responsible for the loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. In the event of early termination of the contract, THE CLIENT undertakes to pay the company the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting, in addition to any applicable penalties, in accordance with the provisions of the conditions of this contract. IV. TERM: The term of the loan and/or lease and/or installment sale will be that agreed upon according to the commercial or promotional conditions or those established in this instrument. V. DELIVERY OF THE EQUIPMENT. In this act, the CLIENT accepts and receives to his satisfaction the equipment in perfect working order, having been inspected and made available to him, prior to its physical delivery.
                            </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <h3>Friendly Summary of Internet Service Contract</h3>
                            <h4>(not part of the contract - for information only)</h4>
                    
                            <h5>Client Information</h5>
                            <p><strong>Name:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Service Address:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Contact:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></p>

                            <h5>Conditions</h5>
                            <p><strong>Length of Contract:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Monthly Payment:</strong> <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{'widget': 'float', 'precision': 2}"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Late Payment Fee:</strong> 5%</p>

                            <h5>Customer Rights and Responsibilities</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Object of the Agreement:</strong> The company will provide Internet browsing services and other additional services through its telecommunications infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Rates, Billing and Payment:</strong> The client will pay the agreed fees on a monthly basis. Invoices will be sent electronically. The client must pay the invoices on the stipulated dates. Failure to receive the invoice does not exempt the obligation to pay.</li>
                                <li><strong>Duration and Termination:</strong> The contract has a specified duration and can be automatically renewed for 12 months if the client does not notify its intention to terminate it with 30 days' notice. The client can cancel the service with 10 days' notice, subject to penalties if canceled before the mandatory term.</li>
                                <li><strong>Ownership and Use of Equipment:</strong> The equipment provided is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contract. In the event of loss or damage to the equipment, the client must notify the company immediately.</li>
                                <li><strong>Equipment Warranty:</strong> The equipment has a manufacturer's warranty and is subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Quality and Maintenance:</strong> The company will provide the services in accordance with the established quality levels and will perform preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Suspension of Services:</strong> The company may suspend services without prior notice in certain cases permitted by law, such as indications of fraud or late payment.</li>
                                <li><strong>Credit Limit:</strong> The company establishes a credit limit for each contracted service, which may be modified at the request of the client.</li>
                                <li><strong>Payment Guarantees:</strong> The client must provide payment guarantees, such as a security, that support the amounts resulting from the services used.</li>
                                <li><strong>Secrecy of Communications:</strong> The company will take measures to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications, but will not be responsible for the illegal obtaining of information by third parties.</li>
                                <li><strong>Assignment of the Contract:</strong> The client cannot assign the contract to third parties without the prior consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to its subsidiaries.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Information:</strong> The company will provide the client with the necessary information for an adequate provision of the service.</li>
                                <li><strong>Validation of Technical Means:</strong> The parties recognize the validity of the electronic data and procedures for the provision of services.</li>
                                <li><strong>Modification of the Contract:</strong> The client may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through the established means.</li>
                                <li><strong>Penalties:</strong> The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper use of the services or breach of contract.</li>
                                <li><strong>Customer Service:</strong> The company offers support through its Service Centers and Call Center.</li>
                                <li><strong>Claims Service:</strong> The client may submit claims related to the provision of services at the Service Centers </li>
                                <li><strong>Applicable Law:</strong> The contract is governed by the laws of the Republic of El Salvador.</li>
                                <li><strong>Maintenance of Contact Information and Notification of Interruptions:</strong> The client must keep his contact information updated and notify the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for damages or loss of service before notification.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Residential Internet Service</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The client will use the service from the assigned protocol number and will guarantee the appropriate electrical installations and equipment.</li>
                                <li>The use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute a violation of current legislation.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Equipment Annex</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The equipment necessary for the provision of services will be provided by the company under conditions of loan, lease or donation subject to conditions.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>
                        </div> 
                    </div>
				</t>
			</t>
		</t>
    </template>
    
<!-- Template for Rental Customers -->
    <template id="rental_contract_template">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
			<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
				<t t-call="web.basic_layout">
					<!-- CONTAINER -->
					<div class="page" style="font-size: 12px">
					    
					    <t t-set="months" t-value="{                             '1': 'enero',                             '2': 'febrero',                             '3': 'marzo',                             '4': 'abril',                             '5': 'mayo',                             '6': 'junio',                             '7': 'julio',                             '8': 'agosto',                             '9': 'septiembre',                             '10': 'octubre',                             '11': 'noviembre',                             '12': 'diciembre'                         }"/>
					    
					    <t t-set="document_types" t-value="{                             'Factura': 'Factura Consumidor Final',                              'CCF': 'Comprobante de Crédito fiscal',                             'FSUJEx': 'Factura de sujeto excluido'                         }"/>
                        
                        <t t-set="tipo_fact" t-value="document_types.get(doc.partner_id.property_account_position_id.sv_document, '')"/>

                        <div class="row mb-4">
                            <div class="col-3">
                                <img t-if="doc.company_id.logo" t-att-src="image_data_uri(doc.company_id.logo)" style="max-height: 100px; margin-left: 2mm" alt="Company Logo"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-5"/>
                            <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                <h5>
                                    <strong>Contract No. </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.cabal_sequence"/>
                                </h5>
                                <h5 class="mt-2">
                                    <strong>Client Code </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.id "/>
                                </h5>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Header -->
                        <h5>CLIENT INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Client Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Client Details</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></div>
                                        <t t-if="tipo_fact == 'Factura Consumidor Final'">
                                            <div>DUI: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_dui"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                        <t t-else="">
                                            <div>NIT: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nit"/></div>
                                            <div>NRC: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nrc"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Service Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Billing Info Header -->
                        <h5>BILLING INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Billing Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Billing Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Contacts</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div>Email: <span class="bg-light p-1"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/></span></div>
                                        <div>Telephone: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/></div>
                                        <div>Whatsapp: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></div>
                                        <div>Telephone Mobile: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.mobile"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row mt-1">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-3">
                                        <strong>Type of Invoicing</strong>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-0">
                                        <span t-esc="tipo_fact"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <!-- Authorization Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-4 font-italic">
                                The client authorizes the delivery of his/her invoice in electronic format by email, SMS or WhatsApp. A copy of the contract conditions will be sent by the same means.
                            </div>

                        </div>
                        
                        <h5>SERVICES CONTRACTED</h5>

                        <!-- Services Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <!-- Get recurring products and total -->
                            <t t-set="recurring_lines" t-value="doc.order_line.filtered(lambda l: l.product_template_id.recurring_invoice)"/>
                            <t t-set="monthly_total" t-value="sum(recurring_lines.mapped('price_unit'))"/>
                            
                            <!-- Products List -->
                            <t t-foreach="recurring_lines" t-as="line">
                                <div class="row mb-2">
                                    <div class="col-12">
                                        <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                            Plan: <t t-esc="line.name"/>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </t>
                        
                            <!-- Contract and Payment Info -->
                            <div class="row mt-3">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Contract Length <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6 text-right">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Monthy Payment: US$ <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <!-- Late Payment Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-3 px-2">
                                Late payment fee - 5%
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    
                        <!-- Declaration Text -->
                        <div class="mt-4" style="font-size: 0.9em;">
                            I declare that my personal information is true and authorize the companies to verify its authenticity, prior to processing the request for services. I accept that the documentation containing the information provided for the purposes of this contract will be safeguarded by the company. I attest to the provisions of this form and annexes. I confirm that I have read and understand the contract and the conditions of the contract, which were presented to me by the company's staff. I ratify the content of the same and sign.
                        </div>
                        
                        <!-- Signature Section -->
                        <div class="mt-4 border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p> 
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Company Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn2/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.user_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                        </div>
                        
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h5 class="m-0">PROMISE WITHOUT PROTEST</h5>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                    Por US$ <strong><t t-esc="doc.contract_value" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/></strong>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                TAMANIQUE, 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.day"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="months[str(doc.start_date.month)]"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.year"/> 
                                We will PAY without protest unconditionally to the order of REDES LITORALES S.A. DE C.V., at its offices, on the _______ day of _________ of the year _________ the amount of
                                <span class="font-weight-bold">
                                    <t t-esc="doc.contract_value_amount_to_text()"/> 
                                    OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
                                </span>, 
                                plus the conventional interest of ONE POINT ZERO ZERO percent per month, calculated from the date of signing of this document, I(we) will also pay, from this last date, default interest on the outstanding principal balance.
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4">
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h4 class="m-0">TERMINOS</h4>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                1. PURPOSE. REDES LITORALES, S.A. de C.V. (hereinafter REDES LITORALES or CABAL), hereinafter referred to as 'the company', shall provide wireless Internet browsing services, dedicated Internet access, and other additional and/or value-added services through its telecommunications infrastructure. The services are provided to the CLIENT in its capacity as recipient or end user thereof, and based on the provisions now established in this document or any of its annexes.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                2. RATES, BILLING AND PAYMENT. The CLIENT shall pay the company the rates corresponding to each of the contracted services, as agreed in the contract. Additionally, the CLIENT shall pay the amounts resulting from any supplementary and/or value-added services used, and the rates for transfers, uninstallations and disconnections. Payments shall be billed in United States dollars, for monthly periods, according to the billing systems used by the company. The CLIENT must pay the invoices on the dates stipulated therein. Such payments may be made at any of the following locations according to preference and availability: CABAL Service Centers, banking and/or financial institutions and/or any other means authorized for this purpose by the company. The corresponding late payment charge will be applied for each service, according to the amount stipulated in the contract. The invoices will reflect the concepts for the services used. Failure to receive the invoice does not inhibit the payment obligation derived from the provision of services, and it is the responsibility of the client to notify the company of this situation. The company, with prior authorization from the client, may deliver invoices by any electronic means. ELECTRONIC BILLING: The sending of invoices by electronic means will be governed by the following conditions: (a) The sending of invoices by electronic means exempts the company from sending the physical invoice to the CLIENT's correspondence address. (b) The company will issue the invoice electronically in accordance with its internal processes and once issued will send it by the electronic means selected by the CLIENT, who will be responsible for the monthly verification of its receipt. (c) The CLIENT recognizes, understands and accepts that it is his responsibility to have the availability to receive the invoice by the electronic means selected by him. (d) In the event that the CLIENT does not receive the invoice in the designated means, his responsibility for payment will not be exempted, and he must also notify the company of this situation. (e) In the event that the CLIENT designates more than one means, the company will give priority to email.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                3. DURATION AND TERMINATION. The duration of the contracted services will be specified in the contract or its annexes. It may be a mandatory or indefinite period, starting from the installation, activation, use and/or programming of the services, and will continue until the client decides to cancel it. 3.1. RIGHT TO UNSUBSCRIBE: The CLIENT has the right to unsubscribe in accordance with the provisions of article 13-8 of the Consumer Protection Law. To make use of such right, THE CLIENT must notify the company ten (10) business days in advance of the time when it is to take effect. In the case of unsubscribing before the expiration of the mandatory period, the penalty established in clause fifteen must be paid. 3.2. CONTINUITY OF SERVICES: Once the agreed mandatory period has ended or when there is no mandatory period agreed by the parties, without the client requesting cancellation, the services will continue to be provided indefinitely, and the client may cancel at any time by notifying ten (10) business days in advance of the time when the cancellation is to take effect, without incurring any penalty. 3.3. GENERAL TERMINATION: The agreed mandatory term may also be terminated by: The general causes of termination of contracts, those established by law, likewise the company will have the right to terminate it in the following cases: a) when the CLIENT improperly uses the services, commits telecommunications fraud or makes illicit use of the services b) When the CLIENT is in arrears for more than two (2) consecutive months, and c) When THE CLIENT requests the provision of services in places other than those established in the contract or in places where the company is physically or technically unable to provide them. The termination of the provision of services will not exempt the CLIENT from its obligations to the company for the goods and services received. THE CLIENT accepts that the company may notify him of the termination of the mandatory term of this contract through technical means according to availability and convenience. 3.4. AUTOMATIC RENEWAL: This contract will automatically renew for an additional period of twelve (12) months at the end of the initial term, unless the CLIENT notifies the company in writing of its intention to terminate the contract at least thirty (30) days prior to the contract end date. The termination notice must be sent by email to cancelservice@cabal.sv or in person at any of the company offices. In the event of automatic renewal, all conditions and terms of the original contract will continue to apply during the renewal period.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                4. ACTIVATION, OWNERSHIP OF EQUIPMENT AND OPERATION OF THE SERVICE. The services will be provided only through the accesses, numbers and/or authorizations that the company delivers or carries out in favor of THE CLIENT. The equipment provided to provide the contracted services will be understood to be delivered to THE CLIENT in the capacity indicated in the contract. The equipment delivered on loan and/or lease is the property of the company. The equipment delivered to THE CLIENT as a purchase, donation or installment sale is the property of THE CLIENT as long as the conditions agreed in this instrument or its annexes are met. The delivery of the equipment, depending on the service, will be carried out through the issuance of a delivery and/or installation order, which will be signed by the user, or failing that, by the person who is at the installation address indicated by the CLIENT. In the event of theft, robbery or loss of the equipment, it is the responsibility of the CUSTOMER to notify the company for the immediate blocking of the services and the corresponding complaint must be filed with the competent authorities, sending a certified copy of the complaint to any of the company's Service Centers within the following five (5) days of its filing. The loss, destruction, deterioration, robbery, theft or misplacement of the equipment does not inhibit the obligation of payment derived from the provision of the services that are available to the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                5. COMMERCIAL WARRANTY. The equipment provided for the provision of services will be covered by the warranty granted by its manufacturers and will therefore be subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product, unless otherwise provided in a special document attached to this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                6. QUALITY, COVERAGE AND MAINTENANCE OF THE SERVICE. The company will provide its services in accordance with the quality levels, parameters and methods established in the current legislation and the conditions of this contract and/or any of its annexes. In any case, the user specifically acknowledges that he/she has all the information regarding the coverage and quality of the services provided. The company will provide the service exclusively in the coverage areas within the national territory in which it is implemented, according to the coverage information of each service available in any of the company's Service Centers. The CUSTOMER understands that mobile services and internet services may be affected by structural, orographic and/or atmospheric conditions, improper handling by the user, number of connected users, or any other situation that prevents, makes impossible or degrades their provision, in which case action will be taken in accordance with the provisions of current legislation. In the case of residential services, THE CUSTOMER acknowledges that they will be provided at the address and domicile provided at the time of contracting. The company will provide preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure, equipment and/or networks for the provision of services, so that, if breakdowns, interruptions or malfunctions of the services occur due to unforeseen circumstances or force majeure, the company will repair the faults or breakdowns that have occurred as soon as possible. The company will not be responsible for damage to the configuration and/or operation of the equipment owned by the user, once the service has been installed/activated to the user's complete satisfaction.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                7. TEMPORARY SUSPENSION OF SERVICES. The company may suspend services without prior notice in cases permitted by current legislation. The company, after giving prior notice to THE CLIENT, may suspend services in the following cases: indication of telecommunications fraud, illicit use of the service or late payment of the client's services. When the company must make a general, temporary and continuous suspension of any of the services, the company will make the corresponding notices in accordance with the law; in these cases, the company will not be responsible for damages caused by the suspension, nor will it be grounds for breach of contract. The CLIENT accepts the limitation of use of any of the services and it will take place when the credit limit has been exceeded, when there are outstanding invoices to be paid or when the blocking of supplementary and/or value-added services has been requested.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                8. CREDIT LIMIT. The company makes available to the CUSTOMER a consumer credit for each contracted service, which will be determined and subsequently modified at the CUSTOMER's request, based on his/her credit behavior.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                9. PAYMENT GUARANTEES. The CLIENT makes available to each service provider a negotiable instrument that will support the payment of the amounts resulting from any of the services used and the total value of the equipment provided. The negotiable instrument will be returned, at the request of the client, within fifteen (15) business days following the effective date of termination of all services, after payment of all outstanding obligations. In addition to the above, the CLIENT will make available to the company any other type of guarantees for the Formation and execution of this contract, which will be contained in documents attached to this instrument.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                10. SECRECY OF COMMUNICATIONS. The company will adopt the necessary technical and organisational measures in accordance with current legislation in order to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications. In any case, the company shall be exonerated from all liability arising from the illegal obtaining of material and/or information, its use or publicity by third parties, and in general, from any actions or omissions, including those of government entities, which, not being attributable to the company, constitute a breach of the secrecy of communications.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                11. ASSIGNMENT. THE CLIENT may not assign this contract, or the services acquired, to third parties without the prior written consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to affiliates and/or subsidiaries belonging to the company.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                12. INFORMATION ABOUT THE SERVICES. The company will provide the CUSTOMER with the necessary and convenient information for an adequate provision of the service, which may be provided on social media, Service Centers, Call Centers, on its website, points of sale or authorized marketers. In the event that the CUSTOMER requests specific information about the provision of the services, the company will provide it free of charge. Likewise, the CUSTOMER agrees to receive information regarding the contracted products and services through technical means such as email, fax, short messages, television, telephone and any other technology that allows remote communication. The CUSTOMER establishes as a means of notification, the physical and electronic addresses, telephone numbers and other data provided in this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                13. VALIDATION OF TECHNICAL MEANS. The parties acknowledge the validity of the electronic and/or telematic data and procedures for the provision and incorporation of services. The client expressly agrees that technical means may be used to express the CLIENT's consent for the modification, incorporation and/or deletion of available services, including value-added services. The CLIENT is responsible for the diligent custody and maintenance of the confidentiality of its information, as well as passwords, access keys, encrypted systems or communication encryption systems, which are provided by the company. These mechanisms will be understood to be used only by the CLIENT.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                14. MODIFICATION OF THE CONTRACT. THE CLIENT may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through any of the means established in clause thirteen (13) of this instrument; once accepted, it will be understood that the terms, conditions, price and term of the same have been agreed upon.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                15. PENALTIES. The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper or illegal use of the services, breach of contract and other causes that are applicable under Salvadoran legislation. In the event of early termination of the mandatory term, the CLIENT must pay the company the value of the goods and services received on the effective date of termination. In turn, the CLIENT will pay the company an amount equivalent to the damage caused by the early termination of the contract as a penalty, which will be an amount equivalent to the basic charges for the services required to terminate the contract; if the client was delivered devices in a quality other than a installment sale, action will be taken in accordance with the equipment annex.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                16. CUSTOMER SERVICE. There is a customer service area available to the CUSTOMER at any of the Service Centers and Call Centers where they can direct requests for information about the contracted services.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                17. HANDLING COMPLAINTS. The CUSTOMER may submit complaints related to the provision of services at the Service Centers provided by the company for this purpose. When the complaint has been resolved, the company will inform the CUSTOMER of the solution adopted through the means designated by the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                18. APPLICABLE LEGISLATION AND DOMICILE. The parties agree that these general conditions and/or their annexes are subject to the legislation of the Republic of El Salvador, and any conflicts arising therefrom are subject to the rules of jurisdiction and competence of common legislation.
                            </div>

                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                19. MAINTENANCE OF CONTACT INFORMATION AND NOTIFICATION OF INTERRUPTIONS. 19.1. The CLIENT agrees to keep his/her address, telephone number and email address up to date. Any change in this information must be communicated to the company immediately. 19.2. The CLIENT must respond to calls, emails or other communications from the company in a timely manner. 19.3. The CLIENT must inform the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for any damage or loss of service that occurs prior to notification. The notification must be sent to the email address meayuda@cabal.sv or notified by telephone, in which case the client will receive a ticket number to record the notification.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                RESIDENTIAL INTERNET SERVICE. The Internet service will be provided under the following conditions: 1) The CUSTOMER will use the service only from the interconnection protocol number assigned by the company and the technical requirements of the CUSTOMER's equipment indicated for this purpose; 2) Continuously, twenty-four hours a day, every day of the year, during the validity of the contracted period for the provision of the service, at the speed established in the selected plan. THE CUSTOMER understands that the navigation speed depends on various technical factors, such as: characteristics and quantity of the equipment connected to the network, incompatibility with other technology or software used by the customer, among others similar, and in case of compensation, action will be taken in accordance with current law. 3) The CUSTOMER will guarantee the electrical installations, associated protection equipment and the appropriate computer equipment to access the service. 4) Under current national and international legislation that ensures intellectual property rights, protection of minors, data protection and others; the use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute an infringement of such legislation; Consequently, the company, by administrative or judicial request, is obliged to reveal the information regarding the ownership of the connection from which the improper use of the network originated. In these cases, the CUSTOMER assumes all responsibility arising from the improper use of the service; 5) The CUSTOMER may at any time improve the contracted service through the various technical means made available by the company.*
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                EQUIPMENT ANNEX. For the purposes of providing the services described in the general contracting conditions, modems, routers, decoder boxes, among others necessary for communications, shall be understood as equipment. The company may make available to the CLIENT, according to the contracted and selected conditions, the equipment in accordance with the following stipulations: l. LOAN CONDITIONS. The company will be the owner of the equipment delivered to the CLIENT for the provision of services, and the CLIENT is obliged to maintain due diligence and care of the same; the latter being responsible for the resulting breakdowns when they are attributable to it; otherwise, the company must replace the goods at the request of the CLIENT and when, at the company's discretion, it is required. Likewise, in the event of restitution of equipment, for example, due to contractual termination, THE CLIENT must return it to the company within a maximum period of ten (10) business days; otherwise, THE CLIENT acknowledges that it must pay the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting. In the event that the CUSTOMER contracts residential services, the following equipment will be delivered on loan: main digital box, Cable Modem, and Router. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. 11. LEASE CONDITIONS. The value of the equipment delivered on lease will be determined, where applicable, in the commercial or promotional conditions. The CUSTOMER acknowledges that the equipment is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contractual relationship. During the duration of the lease, the CUSTOMER is obliged to maintain due diligence and care for it, being responsible for loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. The Customer must pay the administrative cost determined by THE COMPANY for the removal of the equipment. 111. CONDITIONS OF THE DONATION SUBJECT TO CONDITION. The equipment delivered at no cost to THE CLIENT will be deemed free of charge provided that the latter complies with both the general terms and conditions of the contract, as well as the mandatory term of validity. THE CLIENT undertakes to maintain due diligence and care of the equipment, being responsible for the loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. In the event of early termination of the contract, THE CLIENT undertakes to pay the company the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting, in addition to any applicable penalties, in accordance with the provisions of the conditions of this contract. IV. TERM: The term of the loan and/or lease and/or installment sale will be that agreed upon according to the commercial or promotional conditions or those established in this instrument. V. DELIVERY OF THE EQUIPMENT. In this act, the CLIENT accepts and receives to his satisfaction the equipment in perfect working order, having been inspected and made available to him, prior to its physical delivery.
                            </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <h3>Friendly Summary of Internet Service Contract</h3>
                            <h4>(not part of the contract - for information only)</h4>
                    
                            <h5>Client Information</h5>
                            <p><strong>Name:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Service Address:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Contact:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></p>

                            <h5>Conditions</h5>
                            <p><strong>Length of Contract:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Monthly Payment:</strong> <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{'widget': 'float', 'precision': 2}"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Late Payment Fee:</strong> 5%</p>

                            <h5>Customer Rights and Responsibilities</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Object of the Agreement:</strong> The company will provide Internet browsing services and other additional services through its telecommunications infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Rates, Billing and Payment:</strong> The client will pay the agreed fees on a monthly basis. Invoices will be sent electronically. The client must pay the invoices on the stipulated dates. Failure to receive the invoice does not exempt the obligation to pay.</li>
                                <li><strong>Duration and Termination:</strong> The contract has a specified duration and can be automatically renewed for 12 months if the client does not notify its intention to terminate it with 30 days' notice. The client can cancel the service with 10 days' notice, subject to penalties if canceled before the mandatory term.</li>
                                <li><strong>Ownership and Use of Equipment:</strong> The equipment provided is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contract. In the event of loss or damage to the equipment, the client must notify the company immediately.</li>
                                <li><strong>Equipment Warranty:</strong> The equipment has a manufacturer's warranty and is subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Quality and Maintenance:</strong> The company will provide the services in accordance with the established quality levels and will perform preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Suspension of Services:</strong> The company may suspend services without prior notice in certain cases permitted by law, such as indications of fraud or late payment.</li>
                                <li><strong>Credit Limit:</strong> The company establishes a credit limit for each contracted service, which may be modified at the request of the client.</li>
                                <li><strong>Payment Guarantees:</strong> The client must provide payment guarantees, such as a security, that support the amounts resulting from the services used.</li>
                                <li><strong>Secrecy of Communications:</strong> The company will take measures to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications, but will not be responsible for the illegal obtaining of information by third parties.</li>
                                <li><strong>Assignment of the Contract:</strong> The client cannot assign the contract to third parties without the prior consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to its subsidiaries.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Information:</strong> The company will provide the client with the necessary information for an adequate provision of the service.</li>
                                <li><strong>Validation of Technical Means:</strong> The parties recognize the validity of the electronic data and procedures for the provision of services.</li>
                                <li><strong>Modification of the Contract:</strong> The client may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through the established means.</li>
                                <li><strong>Penalties:</strong> The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper use of the services or breach of contract.</li>
                                <li><strong>Customer Service:</strong> The company offers support through its Service Centers and Call Center.</li>
                                <li><strong>Claims Service:</strong> The client may submit claims related to the provision of services at the Service Centers </li>
                                <li><strong>Applicable Law:</strong> The contract is governed by the laws of the Republic of El Salvador.</li>
                                <li><strong>Maintenance of Contact Information and Notification of Interruptions:</strong> The client must keep his contact information updated and notify the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for damages or loss of service before notification.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Residential Internet Service</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The client will use the service from the assigned protocol number and will guarantee the appropriate electrical installations and equipment.</li>
                                <li>The use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute a violation of current legislation.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Equipment Annex</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The equipment necessary for the provision of services will be provided by the company under conditions of loan, lease or donation subject to conditions.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>
                        </div> 
                    </div>
				</t>
			</t>
		</t>
    </template>
    
<!-- Template for IPTV Customers -->
    <template id="iptv_contract_template">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
			<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
				<t t-call="web.basic_layout">
					<!-- CONTAINER -->
					<div class="page" style="font-size: 12px">
					    
					    <t t-set="months" t-value="{                             '1': 'enero',                             '2': 'febrero',                             '3': 'marzo',                             '4': 'abril',                             '5': 'mayo',                             '6': 'junio',                             '7': 'julio',                             '8': 'agosto',                             '9': 'septiembre',                             '10': 'octubre',                             '11': 'noviembre',                             '12': 'diciembre'                         }"/>
					    
					    <t t-set="document_types" t-value="{                             'Factura': 'Factura Consumidor Final',                              'CCF': 'Comprobante de Crédito fiscal',                             'FSUJEx': 'Factura de sujeto excluido'                         }"/>
                        
                        <t t-set="tipo_fact" t-value="document_types.get(doc.partner_id.property_account_position_id.sv_document, '')"/>

                        <div class="row mb-4">
                            <div class="col-3">
                                <img t-if="doc.company_id.logo" t-att-src="image_data_uri(doc.company_id.logo)" style="max-height: 100px; margin-left: 2mm" alt="Company Logo"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-5"/>
                            <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                <h5>
                                    <strong>Contract No. </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.cabal_sequence"/>
                                </h5>
                                <h5 class="mt-2">
                                    <strong>Client Code </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.id "/>
                                </h5>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Header -->
                        <h5>CLIENT INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Client Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Client Details</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></div>
                                        <t t-if="tipo_fact == 'Factura Consumidor Final'">
                                            <div>DUI: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_dui"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                        <t t-else="">
                                            <div>NIT: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nit"/></div>
                                            <div>NRC: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nrc"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Service Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Billing Info Header -->
                        <h5>BILLING INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Billing Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Billing Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Contacts</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div>Email: <span class="bg-light p-1"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/></span></div>
                                        <div>Telephone: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/></div>
                                        <div>Whatsapp: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></div>
                                        <div>Telephone Mobile: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.mobile"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row mt-1">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-3">
                                        <strong>Type of Invoicing</strong>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-0">
                                        <span t-esc="tipo_fact"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <!-- Authorization Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-4 font-italic">
                                The client authorizes the delivery of his/her invoice in electronic format by email, SMS or WhatsApp. A copy of the contract conditions will be sent by the same means.
                            </div>

                        </div>
                        
                        <h5>SERVICES CONTRACTED</h5>

                        <!-- Services Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <!-- Get recurring products and total -->
                            <t t-set="recurring_lines" t-value="doc.order_line.filtered(lambda l: l.product_template_id.recurring_invoice)"/>
                            <t t-set="monthly_total" t-value="sum(recurring_lines.mapped('price_unit'))"/>
                            
                            <!-- Products List -->
                            <t t-foreach="recurring_lines" t-as="line">
                                <div class="row mb-2">
                                    <div class="col-12">
                                        <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                            Plan: <t t-esc="line.name"/>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </t>
                        
                            <!-- Contract and Payment Info -->
                            <div class="row mt-3">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Contract Length <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6 text-right">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Monthy Payment: US$ <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <!-- Late Payment Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-3 px-2">
                                Late payment fee - 5%
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    
                        <!-- Declaration Text -->
                        <div class="mt-4" style="font-size: 0.9em;">
                            I declare that my personal information is true and authorize the companies to verify its authenticity, prior to processing the request for services. I accept that the documentation containing the information provided for the purposes of this contract will be safeguarded by the company. I attest to the provisions of this form and annexes. I confirm that I have read and understand the contract and the conditions of the contract, which were presented to me by the company's staff. I ratify the content of the same and sign.
                        </div>
                        
                        <!-- Signature Section -->
                        <div class="mt-4 border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p> 
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Company Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn2/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.user_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                        </div>
                        
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h5 class="m-0">PROMISE WITHOUT PROTEST</h5>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                    Por US$ <strong><t t-esc="doc.contract_value" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/></strong>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                TAMANIQUE, 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.day"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="months[str(doc.start_date.month)]"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.year"/> 
                                We will PAY without protest unconditionally to the order of REDES LITORALES S.A. DE C.V., at its offices, on the _______ day of _________ of the year _________ the amount of
                                <span class="font-weight-bold">
                                    <t t-esc="doc.contract_value_amount_to_text()"/> 
                                    OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
                                </span>, 
                                plus the conventional interest of ONE POINT ZERO ZERO percent per month, calculated from the date of signing of this document, I(we) will also pay, from this last date, default interest on the outstanding principal balance.
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4">
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h4 class="m-0">TERMINOS</h4>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                1. PURPOSE. REDES LITORALES, S.A. de C.V. (hereinafter REDES LITORALES or CABAL), hereinafter referred to as 'the company', shall provide wireless Internet browsing services, dedicated Internet access, and other additional and/or value-added services through its telecommunications infrastructure. The services are provided to the CLIENT in its capacity as recipient or end user thereof, and based on the provisions now established in this document or any of its annexes.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                2. RATES, BILLING AND PAYMENT. The CLIENT shall pay the company the rates corresponding to each of the contracted services, as agreed in the contract. Additionally, the CLIENT shall pay the amounts resulting from any supplementary and/or value-added services used, and the rates for transfers, uninstallations and disconnections. Payments shall be billed in United States dollars, for monthly periods, according to the billing systems used by the company. The CLIENT must pay the invoices on the dates stipulated therein. Such payments may be made at any of the following locations according to preference and availability: CABAL Service Centers, banking and/or financial institutions and/or any other means authorized for this purpose by the company. The corresponding late payment charge will be applied for each service, according to the amount stipulated in the contract. The invoices will reflect the concepts for the services used. Failure to receive the invoice does not inhibit the payment obligation derived from the provision of services, and it is the responsibility of the client to notify the company of this situation. The company, with prior authorization from the client, may deliver invoices by any electronic means. ELECTRONIC BILLING: The sending of invoices by electronic means will be governed by the following conditions: (a) The sending of invoices by electronic means exempts the company from sending the physical invoice to the CLIENT's correspondence address. (b) The company will issue the invoice electronically in accordance with its internal processes and once issued will send it by the electronic means selected by the CLIENT, who will be responsible for the monthly verification of its receipt. (c) The CLIENT recognizes, understands and accepts that it is his responsibility to have the availability to receive the invoice by the electronic means selected by him. (d) In the event that the CLIENT does not receive the invoice in the designated means, his responsibility for payment will not be exempted, and he must also notify the company of this situation. (e) In the event that the CLIENT designates more than one means, the company will give priority to email.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                3. DURATION AND TERMINATION. The duration of the contracted services will be specified in the contract or its annexes. It may be a mandatory or indefinite period, starting from the installation, activation, use and/or programming of the services, and will continue until the client decides to cancel it. 3.1. RIGHT TO UNSUBSCRIBE: The CLIENT has the right to unsubscribe in accordance with the provisions of article 13-8 of the Consumer Protection Law. To make use of such right, THE CLIENT must notify the company ten (10) business days in advance of the time when it is to take effect. In the case of unsubscribing before the expiration of the mandatory period, the penalty established in clause fifteen must be paid. 3.2. CONTINUITY OF SERVICES: Once the agreed mandatory period has ended or when there is no mandatory period agreed by the parties, without the client requesting cancellation, the services will continue to be provided indefinitely, and the client may cancel at any time by notifying ten (10) business days in advance of the time when the cancellation is to take effect, without incurring any penalty. 3.3. GENERAL TERMINATION: The agreed mandatory term may also be terminated by: The general causes of termination of contracts, those established by law, likewise the company will have the right to terminate it in the following cases: a) when the CLIENT improperly uses the services, commits telecommunications fraud or makes illicit use of the services b) When the CLIENT is in arrears for more than two (2) consecutive months, and c) When THE CLIENT requests the provision of services in places other than those established in the contract or in places where the company is physically or technically unable to provide them. The termination of the provision of services will not exempt the CLIENT from its obligations to the company for the goods and services received. THE CLIENT accepts that the company may notify him of the termination of the mandatory term of this contract through technical means according to availability and convenience. 3.4. AUTOMATIC RENEWAL: This contract will automatically renew for an additional period of twelve (12) months at the end of the initial term, unless the CLIENT notifies the company in writing of its intention to terminate the contract at least thirty (30) days prior to the contract end date. The termination notice must be sent by email to cancelservice@cabal.sv or in person at any of the company offices. In the event of automatic renewal, all conditions and terms of the original contract will continue to apply during the renewal period.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                4. ACTIVATION, OWNERSHIP OF EQUIPMENT AND OPERATION OF THE SERVICE. The services will be provided only through the accesses, numbers and/or authorizations that the company delivers or carries out in favor of THE CLIENT. The equipment provided to provide the contracted services will be understood to be delivered to THE CLIENT in the capacity indicated in the contract. The equipment delivered on loan and/or lease is the property of the company. The equipment delivered to THE CLIENT as a purchase, donation or installment sale is the property of THE CLIENT as long as the conditions agreed in this instrument or its annexes are met. The delivery of the equipment, depending on the service, will be carried out through the issuance of a delivery and/or installation order, which will be signed by the user, or failing that, by the person who is at the installation address indicated by the CLIENT. In the event of theft, robbery or loss of the equipment, it is the responsibility of the CUSTOMER to notify the company for the immediate blocking of the services and the corresponding complaint must be filed with the competent authorities, sending a certified copy of the complaint to any of the company's Service Centers within the following five (5) days of its filing. The loss, destruction, deterioration, robbery, theft or misplacement of the equipment does not inhibit the obligation of payment derived from the provision of the services that are available to the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                5. COMMERCIAL WARRANTY. The equipment provided for the provision of services will be covered by the warranty granted by its manufacturers and will therefore be subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product, unless otherwise provided in a special document attached to this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                6. QUALITY, COVERAGE AND MAINTENANCE OF THE SERVICE. The company will provide its services in accordance with the quality levels, parameters and methods established in the current legislation and the conditions of this contract and/or any of its annexes. In any case, the user specifically acknowledges that he/she has all the information regarding the coverage and quality of the services provided. The company will provide the service exclusively in the coverage areas within the national territory in which it is implemented, according to the coverage information of each service available in any of the company's Service Centers. The CUSTOMER understands that mobile services and internet services may be affected by structural, orographic and/or atmospheric conditions, improper handling by the user, number of connected users, or any other situation that prevents, makes impossible or degrades their provision, in which case action will be taken in accordance with the provisions of current legislation. In the case of residential services, THE CUSTOMER acknowledges that they will be provided at the address and domicile provided at the time of contracting. The company will provide preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure, equipment and/or networks for the provision of services, so that, if breakdowns, interruptions or malfunctions of the services occur due to unforeseen circumstances or force majeure, the company will repair the faults or breakdowns that have occurred as soon as possible. The company will not be responsible for damage to the configuration and/or operation of the equipment owned by the user, once the service has been installed/activated to the user's complete satisfaction.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                7. TEMPORARY SUSPENSION OF SERVICES. The company may suspend services without prior notice in cases permitted by current legislation. The company, after giving prior notice to THE CLIENT, may suspend services in the following cases: indication of telecommunications fraud, illicit use of the service or late payment of the client's services. When the company must make a general, temporary and continuous suspension of any of the services, the company will make the corresponding notices in accordance with the law; in these cases, the company will not be responsible for damages caused by the suspension, nor will it be grounds for breach of contract. The CLIENT accepts the limitation of use of any of the services and it will take place when the credit limit has been exceeded, when there are outstanding invoices to be paid or when the blocking of supplementary and/or value-added services has been requested.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                8. CREDIT LIMIT. The company makes available to the CUSTOMER a consumer credit for each contracted service, which will be determined and subsequently modified at the CUSTOMER's request, based on his/her credit behavior.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                9. PAYMENT GUARANTEES. The CLIENT makes available to each service provider a negotiable instrument that will support the payment of the amounts resulting from any of the services used and the total value of the equipment provided. The negotiable instrument will be returned, at the request of the client, within fifteen (15) business days following the effective date of termination of all services, after payment of all outstanding obligations. In addition to the above, the CLIENT will make available to the company any other type of guarantees for the Formation and execution of this contract, which will be contained in documents attached to this instrument.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                10. SECRECY OF COMMUNICATIONS. The company will adopt the necessary technical and organisational measures in accordance with current legislation in order to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications. In any case, the company shall be exonerated from all liability arising from the illegal obtaining of material and/or information, its use or publicity by third parties, and in general, from any actions or omissions, including those of government entities, which, not being attributable to the company, constitute a breach of the secrecy of communications.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                11. ASSIGNMENT. THE CLIENT may not assign this contract, or the services acquired, to third parties without the prior written consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to affiliates and/or subsidiaries belonging to the company.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                12. INFORMATION ABOUT THE SERVICES. The company will provide the CUSTOMER with the necessary and convenient information for an adequate provision of the service, which may be provided on social media, Service Centers, Call Centers, on its website, points of sale or authorized marketers. In the event that the CUSTOMER requests specific information about the provision of the services, the company will provide it free of charge. Likewise, the CUSTOMER agrees to receive information regarding the contracted products and services through technical means such as email, fax, short messages, television, telephone and any other technology that allows remote communication. The CUSTOMER establishes as a means of notification, the physical and electronic addresses, telephone numbers and other data provided in this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                13. VALIDATION OF TECHNICAL MEANS. The parties acknowledge the validity of the electronic and/or telematic data and procedures for the provision and incorporation of services. The client expressly agrees that technical means may be used to express the CLIENT's consent for the modification, incorporation and/or deletion of available services, including value-added services. The CLIENT is responsible for the diligent custody and maintenance of the confidentiality of its information, as well as passwords, access keys, encrypted systems or communication encryption systems, which are provided by the company. These mechanisms will be understood to be used only by the CLIENT.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                14. MODIFICATION OF THE CONTRACT. THE CLIENT may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through any of the means established in clause thirteen (13) of this instrument; once accepted, it will be understood that the terms, conditions, price and term of the same have been agreed upon.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                15. PENALTIES. The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper or illegal use of the services, breach of contract and other causes that are applicable under Salvadoran legislation. In the event of early termination of the mandatory term, the CLIENT must pay the company the value of the goods and services received on the effective date of termination. In turn, the CLIENT will pay the company an amount equivalent to the damage caused by the early termination of the contract as a penalty, which will be an amount equivalent to the basic charges for the services required to terminate the contract; if the client was delivered devices in a quality other than a installment sale, action will be taken in accordance with the equipment annex.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                16. CUSTOMER SERVICE. There is a customer service area available to the CUSTOMER at any of the Service Centers and Call Centers where they can direct requests for information about the contracted services.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                17. HANDLING COMPLAINTS. The CUSTOMER may submit complaints related to the provision of services at the Service Centers provided by the company for this purpose. When the complaint has been resolved, the company will inform the CUSTOMER of the solution adopted through the means designated by the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                18. APPLICABLE LEGISLATION AND DOMICILE. The parties agree that these general conditions and/or their annexes are subject to the legislation of the Republic of El Salvador, and any conflicts arising therefrom are subject to the rules of jurisdiction and competence of common legislation.
                            </div>

                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                19. MAINTENANCE OF CONTACT INFORMATION AND NOTIFICATION OF INTERRUPTIONS. 19.1. The CLIENT agrees to keep his/her address, telephone number and email address up to date. Any change in this information must be communicated to the company immediately. 19.2. The CLIENT must respond to calls, emails or other communications from the company in a timely manner. 19.3. The CLIENT must inform the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for any damage or loss of service that occurs prior to notification. The notification must be sent to the email address meayuda@cabal.sv or notified by telephone, in which case the client will receive a ticket number to record the notification.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                RESIDENTIAL INTERNET SERVICE. The Internet service will be provided under the following conditions: 1) The CUSTOMER will use the service only from the interconnection protocol number assigned by the company and the technical requirements of the CUSTOMER's equipment indicated for this purpose; 2) Continuously, twenty-four hours a day, every day of the year, during the validity of the contracted period for the provision of the service, at the speed established in the selected plan. THE CUSTOMER understands that the navigation speed depends on various technical factors, such as: characteristics and quantity of the equipment connected to the network, incompatibility with other technology or software used by the customer, among others similar, and in case of compensation, action will be taken in accordance with current law. 3) The CUSTOMER will guarantee the electrical installations, associated protection equipment and the appropriate computer equipment to access the service. 4) Under current national and international legislation that ensures intellectual property rights, protection of minors, data protection and others; the use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute an infringement of such legislation; Consequently, the company, by administrative or judicial request, is obliged to reveal the information regarding the ownership of the connection from which the improper use of the network originated. In these cases, the CUSTOMER assumes all responsibility arising from the improper use of the service; 5) The CUSTOMER may at any time improve the contracted service through the various technical means made available by the company.*
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                EQUIPMENT ANNEX. For the purposes of providing the services described in the general contracting conditions, modems, routers, decoder boxes, among others necessary for communications, shall be understood as equipment. The company may make available to the CLIENT, according to the contracted and selected conditions, the equipment in accordance with the following stipulations: l. LOAN CONDITIONS. The company will be the owner of the equipment delivered to the CLIENT for the provision of services, and the CLIENT is obliged to maintain due diligence and care of the same; the latter being responsible for the resulting breakdowns when they are attributable to it; otherwise, the company must replace the goods at the request of the CLIENT and when, at the company's discretion, it is required. Likewise, in the event of restitution of equipment, for example, due to contractual termination, THE CLIENT must return it to the company within a maximum period of ten (10) business days; otherwise, THE CLIENT acknowledges that it must pay the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting. In the event that the CUSTOMER contracts residential services, the following equipment will be delivered on loan: main digital box, Cable Modem, and Router. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. 11. LEASE CONDITIONS. The value of the equipment delivered on lease will be determined, where applicable, in the commercial or promotional conditions. The CUSTOMER acknowledges that the equipment is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contractual relationship. During the duration of the lease, the CUSTOMER is obliged to maintain due diligence and care for it, being responsible for loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. The Customer must pay the administrative cost determined by THE COMPANY for the removal of the equipment. 111. CONDITIONS OF THE DONATION SUBJECT TO CONDITION. The equipment delivered at no cost to THE CLIENT will be deemed free of charge provided that the latter complies with both the general terms and conditions of the contract, as well as the mandatory term of validity. THE CLIENT undertakes to maintain due diligence and care of the equipment, being responsible for the loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. In the event of early termination of the contract, THE CLIENT undertakes to pay the company the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting, in addition to any applicable penalties, in accordance with the provisions of the conditions of this contract. IV. TERM: The term of the loan and/or lease and/or installment sale will be that agreed upon according to the commercial or promotional conditions or those established in this instrument. V. DELIVERY OF THE EQUIPMENT. In this act, the CLIENT accepts and receives to his satisfaction the equipment in perfect working order, having been inspected and made available to him, prior to its physical delivery.
                            </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <h3>Friendly Summary of Internet Service Contract</h3>
                            <h4>(not part of the contract - for information only)</h4>
                    
                            <h5>Client Information</h5>
                            <p><strong>Name:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Service Address:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Contact:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></p>

                            <h5>Conditions</h5>
                            <p><strong>Length of Contract:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Monthly Payment:</strong> <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{'widget': 'float', 'precision': 2}"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Late Payment Fee:</strong> 5%</p>

                            <h5>Customer Rights and Responsibilities</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Object of the Agreement:</strong> The company will provide Internet browsing services and other additional services through its telecommunications infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Rates, Billing and Payment:</strong> The client will pay the agreed fees on a monthly basis. Invoices will be sent electronically. The client must pay the invoices on the stipulated dates. Failure to receive the invoice does not exempt the obligation to pay.</li>
                                <li><strong>Duration and Termination:</strong> The contract has a specified duration and can be automatically renewed for 12 months if the client does not notify its intention to terminate it with 30 days' notice. The client can cancel the service with 10 days' notice, subject to penalties if canceled before the mandatory term.</li>
                                <li><strong>Ownership and Use of Equipment:</strong> The equipment provided is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contract. In the event of loss or damage to the equipment, the client must notify the company immediately.</li>
                                <li><strong>Equipment Warranty:</strong> The equipment has a manufacturer's warranty and is subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Quality and Maintenance:</strong> The company will provide the services in accordance with the established quality levels and will perform preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Suspension of Services:</strong> The company may suspend services without prior notice in certain cases permitted by law, such as indications of fraud or late payment.</li>
                                <li><strong>Credit Limit:</strong> The company establishes a credit limit for each contracted service, which may be modified at the request of the client.</li>
                                <li><strong>Payment Guarantees:</strong> The client must provide payment guarantees, such as a security, that support the amounts resulting from the services used.</li>
                                <li><strong>Secrecy of Communications:</strong> The company will take measures to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications, but will not be responsible for the illegal obtaining of information by third parties.</li>
                                <li><strong>Assignment of the Contract:</strong> The client cannot assign the contract to third parties without the prior consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to its subsidiaries.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Information:</strong> The company will provide the client with the necessary information for an adequate provision of the service.</li>
                                <li><strong>Validation of Technical Means:</strong> The parties recognize the validity of the electronic data and procedures for the provision of services.</li>
                                <li><strong>Modification of the Contract:</strong> The client may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through the established means.</li>
                                <li><strong>Penalties:</strong> The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper use of the services or breach of contract.</li>
                                <li><strong>Customer Service:</strong> The company offers support through its Service Centers and Call Center.</li>
                                <li><strong>Claims Service:</strong> The client may submit claims related to the provision of services at the Service Centers </li>
                                <li><strong>Applicable Law:</strong> The contract is governed by the laws of the Republic of El Salvador.</li>
                                <li><strong>Maintenance of Contact Information and Notification of Interruptions:</strong> The client must keep his contact information updated and notify the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for damages or loss of service before notification.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Residential Internet Service</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The client will use the service from the assigned protocol number and will guarantee the appropriate electrical installations and equipment.</li>
                                <li>The use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute a violation of current legislation.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Equipment Annex</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The equipment necessary for the provision of services will be provided by the company under conditions of loan, lease or donation subject to conditions.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>
                        </div> 
                    </div>
				</t>
			</t>
		</t>
    </template>
    
<!-- Template for Hotel Customers -->
    <template id="hotel_contract_template">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
			<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
				<t t-call="web.basic_layout">
					<!-- CONTAINER -->
					<div class="page" style="font-size: 12px">
					    
					    <t t-set="months" t-value="{                             '1': 'enero',                             '2': 'febrero',                             '3': 'marzo',                             '4': 'abril',                             '5': 'mayo',                             '6': 'junio',                             '7': 'julio',                             '8': 'agosto',                             '9': 'septiembre',                             '10': 'octubre',                             '11': 'noviembre',                             '12': 'diciembre'                         }"/>
					    
					    <t t-set="document_types" t-value="{                             'Factura': 'Factura Consumidor Final',                              'CCF': 'Comprobante de Crédito fiscal',                             'FSUJEx': 'Factura de sujeto excluido'                         }"/>
                        
                        <t t-set="tipo_fact" t-value="document_types.get(doc.partner_id.property_account_position_id.sv_document, '')"/>

                        <div class="row mb-4">
                            <div class="col-3">
                                <img t-if="doc.company_id.logo" t-att-src="image_data_uri(doc.company_id.logo)" style="max-height: 100px; margin-left: 2mm" alt="Company Logo"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-5"/>
                            <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                <h5>
                                    <strong>Contract No. </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.cabal_sequence"/>
                                </h5>
                                <h5 class="mt-2">
                                    <strong>Client Code </strong>
                                    <span t-esc="doc.id "/>
                                </h5>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Header -->
                        <h5>CLIENT INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Client Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Client Details</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></div>
                                        <t t-if="tipo_fact == 'Factura Consumidor Final'">
                                            <div>DUI: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_dui"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                        <t t-else="">
                                            <div>NIT: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nit"/></div>
                                            <div>NRC: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.sv_nrc"/></div>
                                        </t>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Service Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div class="bg-light"><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Billing Info Header -->
                        <h5>BILLING INFORMATION</h5>

                        <!-- Billing Info Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Billing Address</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.street"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.municipio_dte_sv.name"/></div>
                                        <div><t t-esc="doc.partner_invoice_id.country_id.name"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <strong>Contacts</strong>
                                    <div class="mt-2">
                                        <div>Email: <span class="bg-light p-1"><t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/></span></div>
                                        <div>Telephone: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/></div>
                                        <div>Whatsapp: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></div>
                                        <div>Telephone Mobile: <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.mobile"/></div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row mt-1">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-3">
                                        <strong>Type of Invoicing</strong>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <div class="mt-0">
                                        <span t-esc="tipo_fact"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <!-- Authorization Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-4 font-italic">
                                The client authorizes the delivery of his/her invoice in electronic format by email, SMS or WhatsApp. A copy of the contract conditions will be sent by the same means.
                            </div>

                        </div>
                        
                        <h5>SERVICES CONTRACTED</h5>

                        <!-- Services Box -->
                        <div class="border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <!-- Get recurring products and total -->
                            <t t-set="recurring_lines" t-value="doc.order_line.filtered(lambda l: l.product_template_id.recurring_invoice)"/>
                            <t t-set="monthly_total" t-value="sum(recurring_lines.mapped('price_unit'))"/>
                            
                            <!-- Products List -->
                            <t t-foreach="recurring_lines" t-as="line">
                                <div class="row mb-2">
                                    <div class="col-12">
                                        <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                            Plan: <t t-esc="line.name"/>
                                        </span>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </t>
                        
                            <!-- Contract and Payment Info -->
                            <div class="row mt-3">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Contract Length <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-6 text-right">
                                    <span class="bg-light px-2 py-1">
                                        Monthy Payment: US$ <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/>
                                    </span>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <!-- Late Payment Notice -->
                            <div class="mt-3 px-2">
                                Late payment fee - 5%
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    
                        <!-- Declaration Text -->
                        <div class="mt-4" style="font-size: 0.9em;">
                            I declare that my personal information is true and authorize the companies to verify its authenticity, prior to processing the request for services. I accept that the documentation containing the information provided for the purposes of this contract will be safeguarded by the company. I attest to the provisions of this form and annexes. I confirm that I have read and understand the contract and the conditions of the contract, which were presented to me by the company's staff. I ratify the content of the same and sign.
                        </div>
                        
                        <!-- Signature Section -->
                        <div class="mt-4 border rounded p-3 mb-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p> 
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Company Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn2/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.user_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            
                        </div>
                        
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h5 class="m-0">PROMISE WITHOUT PROTEST</h5>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-end">
                                    Por US$ <strong><t t-esc="doc.contract_value" t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;float&quot;, &quot;precision&quot;: 2}"/></strong>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                TAMANIQUE, 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.day"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="months[str(doc.start_date.month)]"/> de 
                                <t t-esc="doc.start_date.year"/> 
                                We will PAY without protest unconditionally to the order of REDES LITORALES S.A. DE C.V., at its offices, on the _______ day of _________ of the year _________ the amount of
                                <span class="font-weight-bold">
                                    <t t-esc="doc.contract_value_amount_to_text()"/> 
                                    OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
                                </span>, 
                                plus the conventional interest of ONE POINT ZERO ZERO percent per month, calculated from the date of signing of this document, I(we) will also pay, from this last date, default interest on the outstanding principal balance.
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2 text-center">
                                    <p style="font-size: 13px"><strong>Client Signature</strong></p>
                                    <p>/sn1/</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4"/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4 text-start">
                                    <div class="mt-4 border-top pt-2">
                                        <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-2"/>
                                <div class="col-4">
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-6">
                                    <h4 class="m-0">TERMINOS</h4>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        
                            <div class="mt-3 text-justify">
                                1. PURPOSE. REDES LITORALES, S.A. de C.V. (hereinafter REDES LITORALES or CABAL), hereinafter referred to as 'the company', shall provide wireless Internet browsing services, dedicated Internet access, and other additional and/or value-added services through its telecommunications infrastructure. The services are provided to the CLIENT in its capacity as recipient or end user thereof, and based on the provisions now established in this document or any of its annexes.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                2. RATES, BILLING AND PAYMENT. The CLIENT shall pay the company the rates corresponding to each of the contracted services, as agreed in the contract. Additionally, the CLIENT shall pay the amounts resulting from any supplementary and/or value-added services used, and the rates for transfers, uninstallations and disconnections. Payments shall be billed in United States dollars, for monthly periods, according to the billing systems used by the company. The CLIENT must pay the invoices on the dates stipulated therein. Such payments may be made at any of the following locations according to preference and availability: CABAL Service Centers, banking and/or financial institutions and/or any other means authorized for this purpose by the company. The corresponding late payment charge will be applied for each service, according to the amount stipulated in the contract. The invoices will reflect the concepts for the services used. Failure to receive the invoice does not inhibit the payment obligation derived from the provision of services, and it is the responsibility of the client to notify the company of this situation. The company, with prior authorization from the client, may deliver invoices by any electronic means. ELECTRONIC BILLING: The sending of invoices by electronic means will be governed by the following conditions: (a) The sending of invoices by electronic means exempts the company from sending the physical invoice to the CLIENT's correspondence address. (b) The company will issue the invoice electronically in accordance with its internal processes and once issued will send it by the electronic means selected by the CLIENT, who will be responsible for the monthly verification of its receipt. (c) The CLIENT recognizes, understands and accepts that it is his responsibility to have the availability to receive the invoice by the electronic means selected by him. (d) In the event that the CLIENT does not receive the invoice in the designated means, his responsibility for payment will not be exempted, and he must also notify the company of this situation. (e) In the event that the CLIENT designates more than one means, the company will give priority to email.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                3. DURATION AND TERMINATION. The duration of the contracted services will be specified in the contract or its annexes. It may be a mandatory or indefinite period, starting from the installation, activation, use and/or programming of the services, and will continue until the client decides to cancel it. 3.1. RIGHT TO UNSUBSCRIBE: The CLIENT has the right to unsubscribe in accordance with the provisions of article 13-8 of the Consumer Protection Law. To make use of such right, THE CLIENT must notify the company ten (10) business days in advance of the time when it is to take effect. In the case of unsubscribing before the expiration of the mandatory period, the penalty established in clause fifteen must be paid. 3.2. CONTINUITY OF SERVICES: Once the agreed mandatory period has ended or when there is no mandatory period agreed by the parties, without the client requesting cancellation, the services will continue to be provided indefinitely, and the client may cancel at any time by notifying ten (10) business days in advance of the time when the cancellation is to take effect, without incurring any penalty. 3.3. GENERAL TERMINATION: The agreed mandatory term may also be terminated by: The general causes of termination of contracts, those established by law, likewise the company will have the right to terminate it in the following cases: a) when the CLIENT improperly uses the services, commits telecommunications fraud or makes illicit use of the services b) When the CLIENT is in arrears for more than two (2) consecutive months, and c) When THE CLIENT requests the provision of services in places other than those established in the contract or in places where the company is physically or technically unable to provide them. The termination of the provision of services will not exempt the CLIENT from its obligations to the company for the goods and services received. THE CLIENT accepts that the company may notify him of the termination of the mandatory term of this contract through technical means according to availability and convenience. 3.4. AUTOMATIC RENEWAL: This contract will automatically renew for an additional period of twelve (12) months at the end of the initial term, unless the CLIENT notifies the company in writing of its intention to terminate the contract at least thirty (30) days prior to the contract end date. The termination notice must be sent by email to cancelservice@cabal.sv or in person at any of the company offices. In the event of automatic renewal, all conditions and terms of the original contract will continue to apply during the renewal period.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                4. ACTIVATION, OWNERSHIP OF EQUIPMENT AND OPERATION OF THE SERVICE. The services will be provided only through the accesses, numbers and/or authorizations that the company delivers or carries out in favor of THE CLIENT. The equipment provided to provide the contracted services will be understood to be delivered to THE CLIENT in the capacity indicated in the contract. The equipment delivered on loan and/or lease is the property of the company. The equipment delivered to THE CLIENT as a purchase, donation or installment sale is the property of THE CLIENT as long as the conditions agreed in this instrument or its annexes are met. The delivery of the equipment, depending on the service, will be carried out through the issuance of a delivery and/or installation order, which will be signed by the user, or failing that, by the person who is at the installation address indicated by the CLIENT. In the event of theft, robbery or loss of the equipment, it is the responsibility of the CUSTOMER to notify the company for the immediate blocking of the services and the corresponding complaint must be filed with the competent authorities, sending a certified copy of the complaint to any of the company's Service Centers within the following five (5) days of its filing. The loss, destruction, deterioration, robbery, theft or misplacement of the equipment does not inhibit the obligation of payment derived from the provision of the services that are available to the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                5. COMMERCIAL WARRANTY. The equipment provided for the provision of services will be covered by the warranty granted by its manufacturers and will therefore be subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product, unless otherwise provided in a special document attached to this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                6. QUALITY, COVERAGE AND MAINTENANCE OF THE SERVICE. The company will provide its services in accordance with the quality levels, parameters and methods established in the current legislation and the conditions of this contract and/or any of its annexes. In any case, the user specifically acknowledges that he/she has all the information regarding the coverage and quality of the services provided. The company will provide the service exclusively in the coverage areas within the national territory in which it is implemented, according to the coverage information of each service available in any of the company's Service Centers. The CUSTOMER understands that mobile services and internet services may be affected by structural, orographic and/or atmospheric conditions, improper handling by the user, number of connected users, or any other situation that prevents, makes impossible or degrades their provision, in which case action will be taken in accordance with the provisions of current legislation. In the case of residential services, THE CUSTOMER acknowledges that they will be provided at the address and domicile provided at the time of contracting. The company will provide preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure, equipment and/or networks for the provision of services, so that, if breakdowns, interruptions or malfunctions of the services occur due to unforeseen circumstances or force majeure, the company will repair the faults or breakdowns that have occurred as soon as possible. The company will not be responsible for damage to the configuration and/or operation of the equipment owned by the user, once the service has been installed/activated to the user's complete satisfaction.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                7. TEMPORARY SUSPENSION OF SERVICES. The company may suspend services without prior notice in cases permitted by current legislation. The company, after giving prior notice to THE CLIENT, may suspend services in the following cases: indication of telecommunications fraud, illicit use of the service or late payment of the client's services. When the company must make a general, temporary and continuous suspension of any of the services, the company will make the corresponding notices in accordance with the law; in these cases, the company will not be responsible for damages caused by the suspension, nor will it be grounds for breach of contract. The CLIENT accepts the limitation of use of any of the services and it will take place when the credit limit has been exceeded, when there are outstanding invoices to be paid or when the blocking of supplementary and/or value-added services has been requested.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                8. CREDIT LIMIT. The company makes available to the CUSTOMER a consumer credit for each contracted service, which will be determined and subsequently modified at the CUSTOMER's request, based on his/her credit behavior.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                9. PAYMENT GUARANTEES. The CLIENT makes available to each service provider a negotiable instrument that will support the payment of the amounts resulting from any of the services used and the total value of the equipment provided. The negotiable instrument will be returned, at the request of the client, within fifteen (15) business days following the effective date of termination of all services, after payment of all outstanding obligations. In addition to the above, the CLIENT will make available to the company any other type of guarantees for the Formation and execution of this contract, which will be contained in documents attached to this instrument.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                10. SECRECY OF COMMUNICATIONS. The company will adopt the necessary technical and organisational measures in accordance with current legislation in order to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications. In any case, the company shall be exonerated from all liability arising from the illegal obtaining of material and/or information, its use or publicity by third parties, and in general, from any actions or omissions, including those of government entities, which, not being attributable to the company, constitute a breach of the secrecy of communications.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                11. ASSIGNMENT. THE CLIENT may not assign this contract, or the services acquired, to third parties without the prior written consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to affiliates and/or subsidiaries belonging to the company.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                12. INFORMATION ABOUT THE SERVICES. The company will provide the CUSTOMER with the necessary and convenient information for an adequate provision of the service, which may be provided on social media, Service Centers, Call Centers, on its website, points of sale or authorized marketers. In the event that the CUSTOMER requests specific information about the provision of the services, the company will provide it free of charge. Likewise, the CUSTOMER agrees to receive information regarding the contracted products and services through technical means such as email, fax, short messages, television, telephone and any other technology that allows remote communication. The CUSTOMER establishes as a means of notification, the physical and electronic addresses, telephone numbers and other data provided in this contract.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                13. VALIDATION OF TECHNICAL MEANS. The parties acknowledge the validity of the electronic and/or telematic data and procedures for the provision and incorporation of services. The client expressly agrees that technical means may be used to express the CLIENT's consent for the modification, incorporation and/or deletion of available services, including value-added services. The CLIENT is responsible for the diligent custody and maintenance of the confidentiality of its information, as well as passwords, access keys, encrypted systems or communication encryption systems, which are provided by the company. These mechanisms will be understood to be used only by the CLIENT.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                14. MODIFICATION OF THE CONTRACT. THE CLIENT may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through any of the means established in clause thirteen (13) of this instrument; once accepted, it will be understood that the terms, conditions, price and term of the same have been agreed upon.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                15. PENALTIES. The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper or illegal use of the services, breach of contract and other causes that are applicable under Salvadoran legislation. In the event of early termination of the mandatory term, the CLIENT must pay the company the value of the goods and services received on the effective date of termination. In turn, the CLIENT will pay the company an amount equivalent to the damage caused by the early termination of the contract as a penalty, which will be an amount equivalent to the basic charges for the services required to terminate the contract; if the client was delivered devices in a quality other than a installment sale, action will be taken in accordance with the equipment annex.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                16. CUSTOMER SERVICE. There is a customer service area available to the CUSTOMER at any of the Service Centers and Call Centers where they can direct requests for information about the contracted services.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                17. HANDLING COMPLAINTS. The CUSTOMER may submit complaints related to the provision of services at the Service Centers provided by the company for this purpose. When the complaint has been resolved, the company will inform the CUSTOMER of the solution adopted through the means designated by the CUSTOMER.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                18. APPLICABLE LEGISLATION AND DOMICILE. The parties agree that these general conditions and/or their annexes are subject to the legislation of the Republic of El Salvador, and any conflicts arising therefrom are subject to the rules of jurisdiction and competence of common legislation.
                            </div>

                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                19. MAINTENANCE OF CONTACT INFORMATION AND NOTIFICATION OF INTERRUPTIONS. 19.1. The CLIENT agrees to keep his/her address, telephone number and email address up to date. Any change in this information must be communicated to the company immediately. 19.2. The CLIENT must respond to calls, emails or other communications from the company in a timely manner. 19.3. The CLIENT must inform the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for any damage or loss of service that occurs prior to notification. The notification must be sent to the email address meayuda@cabal.sv or notified by telephone, in which case the client will receive a ticket number to record the notification.
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                RESIDENTIAL INTERNET SERVICE. The Internet service will be provided under the following conditions: 1) The CUSTOMER will use the service only from the interconnection protocol number assigned by the company and the technical requirements of the CUSTOMER's equipment indicated for this purpose; 2) Continuously, twenty-four hours a day, every day of the year, during the validity of the contracted period for the provision of the service, at the speed established in the selected plan. THE CUSTOMER understands that the navigation speed depends on various technical factors, such as: characteristics and quantity of the equipment connected to the network, incompatibility with other technology or software used by the customer, among others similar, and in case of compensation, action will be taken in accordance with current law. 3) The CUSTOMER will guarantee the electrical installations, associated protection equipment and the appropriate computer equipment to access the service. 4) Under current national and international legislation that ensures intellectual property rights, protection of minors, data protection and others; the use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute an infringement of such legislation; Consequently, the company, by administrative or judicial request, is obliged to reveal the information regarding the ownership of the connection from which the improper use of the network originated. In these cases, the CUSTOMER assumes all responsibility arising from the improper use of the service; 5) The CUSTOMER may at any time improve the contracted service through the various technical means made available by the company.*
                            </div>
                            
                            <div class="mt-1 text-justify">
                                EQUIPMENT ANNEX. For the purposes of providing the services described in the general contracting conditions, modems, routers, decoder boxes, among others necessary for communications, shall be understood as equipment. The company may make available to the CLIENT, according to the contracted and selected conditions, the equipment in accordance with the following stipulations: l. LOAN CONDITIONS. The company will be the owner of the equipment delivered to the CLIENT for the provision of services, and the CLIENT is obliged to maintain due diligence and care of the same; the latter being responsible for the resulting breakdowns when they are attributable to it; otherwise, the company must replace the goods at the request of the CLIENT and when, at the company's discretion, it is required. Likewise, in the event of restitution of equipment, for example, due to contractual termination, THE CLIENT must return it to the company within a maximum period of ten (10) business days; otherwise, THE CLIENT acknowledges that it must pay the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting. In the event that the CUSTOMER contracts residential services, the following equipment will be delivered on loan: main digital box, Cable Modem, and Router. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. 11. LEASE CONDITIONS. The value of the equipment delivered on lease will be determined, where applicable, in the commercial or promotional conditions. The CUSTOMER acknowledges that the equipment is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contractual relationship. During the duration of the lease, the CUSTOMER is obliged to maintain due diligence and care for it, being responsible for loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. The company may arrange a different way of acquiring the equipment in accordance with the observations described in the contract. The Customer must pay the administrative cost determined by THE COMPANY for the removal of the equipment. 111. CONDITIONS OF THE DONATION SUBJECT TO CONDITION. The equipment delivered at no cost to THE CLIENT will be deemed free of charge provided that the latter complies with both the general terms and conditions of the contract, as well as the mandatory term of validity. THE CLIENT undertakes to maintain due diligence and care of the equipment, being responsible for the loss, misplacement, destruction, breakdowns, theft, robbery or other resulting causes when they are attributable to him. In the event of early termination of the contract, THE CLIENT undertakes to pay the company the market value of the equipment at the time of contracting, in addition to any applicable penalties, in accordance with the provisions of the conditions of this contract. IV. TERM: The term of the loan and/or lease and/or installment sale will be that agreed upon according to the commercial or promotional conditions or those established in this instrument. V. DELIVERY OF THE EQUIPMENT. In this act, the CLIENT accepts and receives to his satisfaction the equipment in perfect working order, having been inspected and made available to him, prior to its physical delivery.
                            </div>
                        <div style="page-break-before: always;"></div>
                        <div class="border rounded p-4 mt-4">
                            <h3>Friendly Summary of Internet Service Contract</h3>
                            <h4>(not part of the contract - for information only)</h4>
                    
                            <h5>Client Information</h5>
                            <p><strong>Name:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Service Address:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_shipping_id.street"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Contact:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.email"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.phone"/>, <t t-esc="doc.partner_id.whatsapp"/></p>

                            <h5>Conditions</h5>
                            <p><strong>Length of Contract:</strong> <t t-esc="doc.contract_term.name"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Monthly Payment:</strong> <t t-esc="monthly_total" t-options="{'widget': 'float', 'precision': 2}"/></p>
                            <p><strong>Late Payment Fee:</strong> 5%</p>

                            <h5>Customer Rights and Responsibilities</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Object of the Agreement:</strong> The company will provide Internet browsing services and other additional services through its telecommunications infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Rates, Billing and Payment:</strong> The client will pay the agreed fees on a monthly basis. Invoices will be sent electronically. The client must pay the invoices on the stipulated dates. Failure to receive the invoice does not exempt the obligation to pay.</li>
                                <li><strong>Duration and Termination:</strong> The contract has a specified duration and can be automatically renewed for 12 months if the client does not notify its intention to terminate it with 30 days' notice. The client can cancel the service with 10 days' notice, subject to penalties if canceled before the mandatory term.</li>
                                <li><strong>Ownership and Use of Equipment:</strong> The equipment provided is the property of the company and must be returned at the end of the contract. In the event of loss or damage to the equipment, the client must notify the company immediately.</li>
                                <li><strong>Equipment Warranty:</strong> The equipment has a manufacturer's warranty and is subject to the terms and conditions of the purchased product.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Quality and Maintenance:</strong> The company will provide the services in accordance with the established quality levels and will perform preventive and corrective maintenance of its infrastructure.</li>
                                <li><strong>Suspension of Services:</strong> The company may suspend services without prior notice in certain cases permitted by law, such as indications of fraud or late payment.</li>
                                <li><strong>Credit Limit:</strong> The company establishes a credit limit for each contracted service, which may be modified at the request of the client.</li>
                                <li><strong>Payment Guarantees:</strong> The client must provide payment guarantees, such as a security, that support the amounts resulting from the services used.</li>
                                <li><strong>Secrecy of Communications:</strong> The company will take measures to guarantee the secrecy of telecommunications, but will not be responsible for the illegal obtaining of information by third parties.</li>
                                <li><strong>Assignment of the Contract:</strong> The client cannot assign the contract to third parties without the prior consent of the company. The company may assign the contract to its subsidiaries.</li>
                                <li><strong>Service Information:</strong> The company will provide the client with the necessary information for an adequate provision of the service.</li>
                                <li><strong>Validation of Technical Means:</strong> The parties recognize the validity of the electronic data and procedures for the provision of services.</li>
                                <li><strong>Modification of the Contract:</strong> The client may make additions or improvements to the contracted services, accepting them through the established means.</li>
                                <li><strong>Penalties:</strong> The company may establish penalties for early termination, improper use of the services or breach of contract.</li>
                                <li><strong>Customer Service:</strong> The company offers support through its Service Centers and Call Center.</li>
                                <li><strong>Claims Service:</strong> The client may submit claims related to the provision of services at the Service Centers </li>
                                <li><strong>Applicable Law:</strong> The contract is governed by the laws of the Republic of El Salvador.</li>
                                <li><strong>Maintenance of Contact Information and Notification of Interruptions:</strong> The client must keep his contact information updated and notify the company of any interruption in service immediately. The company will not be responsible for damages or loss of service before notification.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Residential Internet Service</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The client will use the service from the assigned protocol number and will guarantee the appropriate electrical installations and equipment.</li>
                                <li>The use and/or downloading of illegal content may constitute a violation of current legislation.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h5>Equipment Annex</h5>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The equipment necessary for the provision of services will be provided by the company under conditions of loan, lease or donation subject to conditions.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>
                        </div> 
                    </div>
				</t>
			</t>
		</t>
    </template>
</odoo>